Do not use the flash to take pictures during the tour
ツアー中の写真撮影にはフラッシュを使用しないでください
Thank you for your cooperation
ご協力ありがとうございます
Also, what about the Academia Sinica?
また、中央研究院はどうでしょうか？
We will also share the audio and video of the live broadcast of our past knowledge feast
過去の知識の饗宴の生放送の音声とビデオも共有します。
put it on youtube
youtubeに載せて
So if everyone after the speech
それで、スピーチの後、全員が
If you want to relive the essence of past speeches
過去のスピーチのエッセンスをもう一度味わいたい場合
You can search Academia Sinica directly on YouTube
YouTube で中央研究院を直接検索できます
You can watch videos of our past speeches
過去の講演動画をご覧いただけます
Thanks
ありがとう
Do not take photos with flash
フラッシュを使用して写真を撮らないでください
instrument enrolled
登録された機器
Hosted by Vice President Fu Dong
副総統の福東氏が主催
thank you
ありがとう
Welcome and thank you for participating in this month's feast of knowledge
ようこそ、今月の知識の饗宴にご参加いただきありがとうございます
Our main award today is Pan Wenhan, a special review researcher
本日の主な賞は、特別レビュー研究者のパン・ウェンハン氏です。
Professor Pan Wenhan
潘文漢教授
Cornell University PhD in Nutritional Epidemiology
コーネル大学栄養疫学の博士号
acquired in 1983
1983年に取得
He is at Northwestern University
彼はノースウェスタン大学にいます
it's a north
それは北です
A Northwestern University
ノースウェスタン大学
Department of Community Health and Preventive Medicine
地域保健予防医学科
postdoctoral research
博士研究員
Returned to China in 1987
1987年に中国に帰国
Into the service of Central Medical College
中央医科大学に勤務
Institute of Biomedical Sciences
生物医科学研究所
He is now a special researcher at the firm
彼は現在、その会社の特別研究員です
Dr. Pan's field of research
パン博士の研究分野
nutritional epidemiology
栄養疫学
His field of very distinguished research is
彼の非常に優れた研究分野は、
Cardiovascular disease and nutrition
心血管疾患と栄養
I think he will share this topic with us today
今日彼はこの話題を私たちに共有してくれると思います
has published more than 300 papers
300以上の論文を発表しています
He also received many awards
数々の賞も受賞している
Important awards include the 2004
重要な賞には 2004 年が含まれます。
Outstanding Research Award from Taiwan Nutrition Society
台湾栄養学会より優秀研究賞を受賞
Received Lifetime Achievement Award from Asia Pacific Society of Clinical Nutrition in 2010
2010 年に、アジア太平洋臨床栄養学会から生涯功績賞を受賞しました。
In 2015, he was awarded the Outstanding Contribution Award for Science and Technology by the Executive Yuan
2015年に行政院より科学技術功労賞を受賞
The last Executive Yuan is the Executive Yuan
最後の行政院は行政院です
One of the highest honors in academia
学術界で最高の栄誉の一つ
Alright then we welcome Professor Pan Wan now
さて、それではパン・ワン教授をお迎えします
good night ladies and gentlemen
おやすみなさい、紳士淑女の皆様
first of all thank you very much
まず初めに、ありがとうございます
Thank you, Vice President Liu, for inviting me to the feast of knowledge
劉副大統領、知識の饗宴にご招待いただきありがとうございます
Let me share with you today's topic
今日のトピックを共有させてください
Vice President Liu is actually my old officer.
劉副大統領は実は私の昔の役員です。
is the director of our Institute of Biomedical Sciences
私たちの生物医学研究所の所長です
So he recommended me to speak
それで彼は私に話すように勧めた
I also cherish such an opportunity very much.
私もこのような機会をとても大切にしています。
To be able to work with colleagues in our hospital
当院の同僚と協力して働けるようにするため
Or some friends from the community to talk about
またはコミュニティの友達と話しましょう
Citation vitality eats out this topic
引用の活力がこの話題を食いつぶす
This is a very important topic now
これは今非常に重要なテーマです
because of medical advances
医療の進歩のせいで
the improvement of economic life
経済生活の改善
Now everyone pays more and more attention to health
今、誰もが健康にますます注目しています
So the elderly are very, very
ですから、お年寄りはとても、とても
very many
非常に多くの
But what about some of the health problems encountered by old age?
しかし、高齢になると直面する健康上の問題についてはどうでしょうか?
actually some
実際にはいくつか
In other words, there is no way to go deep into the research.
言い換えれば、研究を深く掘り下げる方法はありません。
there are many things we don't know
私たちが知らないことがたくさんあります
I am very happy to talk about this topic today
今日はこのテーマについてお話しできることをとてもうれしく思います
So today I mainly tell you about this content
ということで今日はこの内容を中心にお伝えします
Layer these parts
これらのパーツを重ねていきます
when i will start
いつ始めますか
because we speak of vitality
私たちは活力について話しているので
In fact, another aspect of vitality is weakness.
実際、活力のもう一つの側面は弱さです。
how not to weaken
弱らせない方法
Maybe it's the other side of vitality
それは活力の裏側なのかもしれない
So I'm going to tell you first
だから最初に言っておきます
incapacity
無能力
and the phenomenon of geriatric syndrome
そして老人症候群という現象
so you might be clearer
そうすればもっと明確になるかもしれません
How can we make the Citing French family
どうすれば引用フランス人家族を作ることができますか
still live with such vitality
今でもそのような活力を持って生きています
That's another
さらに、それは
For our comparison there may be some
私たちの比較のために、いくつかあるかもしれません
What about the younger audience?
若い視聴者はどうですか？
I can learn about the aging process
老化の過程を知ることができる
Changes in our bodies and our bodies
私たちの体と体の変化
so maybe even middle age
だから中年でもいいかもしれない
followed by young
続いて若者
you can think at this time
この時点で考えることができます
how do i keep healthy
どうすれば健康を保てますか
So when I go to Citing the French
それで私がCiting Frenchに行くとき
I can be at my best
私は最高の状態になれる
After understanding this
これを理解した上で
Maybe we'll be motivated
もしかしたらモチベーションも上がるかも知れません
there will be a motive
動機があるだろう
So what am I going to do?
それで、私は何をするつもりですか？
to avoid such an aging process
このような老化現象を避けるために
So I will talk about some of the main content of today
それでは今日の主な内容についてお話します
It's something related to frailty
虚弱に関連する
Factors in a Nutritious Diet
栄養価の高い食事の要素
Of course I don't want to talk like a lecture
もちろん講義みたいな話はしたくない
Everyone just listened to the textbook
みんなただ教科書を聞いただけ
should be like this should be like that
こうあるべきだ こうあるべきだ
so why do i say that
それでなぜ私がそんなことを言うのですか
Some of our empirical research
私たちの実証研究の一部
I will also introduce to you a little
こちらも少しご紹介させていただきます
that apart from debility
それは衰弱とは別に
I'll talk a little bit about coercion
強制について少しお話します
Because of weakness and restraint
弱さと抑制のせいで
This is in geriatric syndrome
これは老人症候群です
most common most important
最も一般的な最も重要な
So these nutrients
そこで、これらの栄養素を
After this knowledge is introduced
この知識を導入した後、
I'll tell you a little bit
少し教えてあげる
We are currently applying this knowledge to the community
私たちは現在、この知識をコミュニティに適用しています
A few simple photos to tell everyone
みんなに伝えるための簡単な写真をいくつか
we have some community residents
コミュニティ住民が何人かいます
have begun to absorb this knowledge
この知識を吸収し始めました
do something like this one
このようなことをしてください
a practical operation
実際の操作
ok that is
わかりました、それは
Today's main content
本日の主な内容
Finally, I will tell you
最後にお伝えします
Our Academia Sinica has an Academia Sinica nutrition information website
私たちの中央研究院には、中央研究院の栄養情報ウェブサイトがあります。
The information in the middle can be used by everyone
真ん中の情報は誰でも利用できます
in myself and in my family
自分自身と家族の中で
Okay, what we're talking about today
さて、今日は何について話しますか
I also want to tell you
私もあなたに伝えたいです
A lot of the knowledge we talked about today
今日話した多くの知識
It is because of a sustainable project of Academia Sinica
それは中央研究院の持続可能なプロジェクトによるものです
so some get some new knowledge
新しい知識を得る人もいます
In addition, a lot of information is also from the National Health Service
さらに、国民保健サービスからも多くの情報が提供されます。
Some information from our Taiwan Nutrition and Health Survey
台湾の栄養と健康に関する調査からの情報
Allows us to do some data mining
いくつかのデータマイニングを行うことができます
In the community care base just mentioned
先ほどの地域ケア拠点では
We are already doing some dietary interventions
私たちはすでにいくつかの食事介入を行っています
That's because the nutritional status and dietary patterns of the elderly from the National Health Service
それは、国民保健サービスが提供する高齢者の栄養状態と食事パターンによるものです。
Correlation studies with various geriatric syndromes
さまざまな老年症候群との相関研究
Then here are some of my partners
それでは私のパートナーを何人か紹介します
A lot of what I'm talking about today is them with me
今日私が話していることの多くは、彼らが私と一緒にいるということです
made
作る
then first let me talk
それではまず話させてください
Frailty and disability and geriatric syndrome
フレイルと障害と老人症候群
Then let me tell you about us alone
それなら私たち二人だけのことを話しましょう
How do we human beings enter a state of incapacity or weakness
私たち人間はどのようにして無力または弱さの状態に陥るのでしょうか
And what is the relationship between disability and weakness?
そして、障害と弱さの間にはどのような関係があるのでしょうか？
I don't know if you can see this picture clearly
この写真をはっきりと見てもらえるかわかりませんが、
That is to say, we humans can divide it into
つまり、私たち人間は次のように分けることができます。
Use this line to make a distinction
区別するにはこの行を使用します
This place is an old man's function index
ここは老人の機能索引です
So when someone with your better function
だから、誰かがあなたのより優れた機能を持っているとき、
If you face a small illness
小さな病気に直面したら
your function may be reduced
あなたの機能が低下する可能性があります
That's because he recovered from his illness and returned to health
それは彼が病気から回復し健康を取り戻したからです
But if our body is in a relatively weak state
しかし、私たちの体が比較的弱い状態にある場合、
I may have a cold, diarrhea or bad teeth
風邪をひいたり、下痢をしたり、歯が悪くなったりするかもしれません
Possibly the function will drop in a very short time
おそらく機能は短期間で低下するでしょう
to a state where there may be no way to drop
落とす方法がないかもしれない状態に
into a state of dependence
依存状態に陥る
So everyone knows the geriatric syndrome we are talking about today
今日私たちが話している老人症候群については誰もが知っています
In fact, he is not a problem encountered by people in their fifties and sixties.
実際、彼は50代や60代の人が直面する問題ではありません。
but usually older
でも普通は年上
People in their seventies and eighties
70代、80代の人たち
that you have been very healthy all your life
あなたは今までずっととても健康だったということ
no cardiovascular disease
心血管疾患がないこと
nothing sick
何も病気ではありません
a situation you will also encounter
あなたも遭遇するであろう状況
So is one such a reference method code by code
そのような参照メソッドの 1 つはコードごとにあります
We're talking about something like this
私たちはこのようなことについて話しています
so that means
つまり
One should try to maintain one's own function
人は自分自身の機能を維持するよう努めるべきである
is in good condition
状態は良好です
so you don't run into little ailments
小さな病気に遭わないように
When challenged, it falls into a so-called
挑戦すると、いわゆる
into a state of dependence
依存状態に陥る
just dependent
ただ依存しているだけ
Then you have to rely on someone else's state
そうなると、他人の状態に依存する必要があります
Or lie in bed and never get up again
あるいはベッドに横たわって二度と起き上がれない
But how do we approach this issue?
しかし、この問題にどのようにアプローチすればよいでしょうか?
What about the picture I showed you here?
ここで見せた写真はどうでしょうか？
is a state that shows the aging of us alone
それは私たちだけが老化していることを示す状態です
We are generally healthier people
私たちは一般的により健康な人々です
It is a gradual degeneration of function
徐々に機能が低下していきます
Then it must be maintained under a normal life
それから、それは通常の生活の下で維持されなければなりません
probably such a very healthy energy
おそらくとても健康的なエネルギーだと思います
to very old age
非常に高齢になるまで
it enters into a state of weakness
それは衰弱状態に入る
so that aging
それで老化する
What about the ones who sustain better?
より良く持続できる人たちはどうなるでしょうか？
It's the red line that's always been level.
常に水平になっている赤い線です。
May be there are some very healthy people
中にはとても健康な人もいるかもしれない
to one hundred years old
百歳まで
When I was over a hundred years old
百歳を超えたとき
It is possible that this function line will suddenly drop
この関数行が突然ドロップされる可能性があります
and then move on to the next stage of life
そして人生の次のステージに進む
But what if a person with a lot of pain
しかし、ひどい痛みを抱えている人がいたらどうなるでしょうか？
it follows the curve that tends to be
傾向のある曲線に従います。
That is to say, its functionality degrades rapidly
つまり、機能が急激に劣化してしまうのです。
when it's not too old
あまり古くないとき
into a state of weakness
衰弱状態に陥る
So because it's in a weakened state
弱っている状態なので
It is easy to enter into incapacity
無能力状態に陥りやすい
It's about reaching this final stage of life.
それは人生の最終段階に到達することです。
And so of course we want to say
そしてもちろん、私たちが言いたいのは、
to keep as much as possible
できるだけ保つように
a state of robustness and vitality
丈夫さと活力のある状態
Then maintain the red line to the highest
その後、赤いラインを最高値まで維持します
don't then finally if it's going to fall
落ちるつもりなら最後にはやめてください
also in the shortest possible time
それも可能な限り最短で
fall down it's a so-called
落ちる、いわゆる
Healthy
健康
That is to say, health and longevity
つまり、健康と長寿
means you can put your
あなたのものを置くことができることを意味します
this time of life
人生のこの時期
maintain a peak
ピークを維持する
the longer the better
長いほど良い
Then if what is going to drop is in a very short time
そして、もしそれが非常に短期間に落ちるとしたら
If such a situation of falling
このような転倒の状況になった場合
so aging
とても老化している
aging process
老化の過程
eventually debilitating
最終的に衰弱する
if you are in a debilitated state
衰弱した状態にある場合
if any event occurs
何かイベントが起きたら
The event can be a fall
イベントは秋になる可能性があります
Cold or crab belly or bad teeth
風邪かカニ腹か歯が悪いか
What if you're in a debilitated state?
衰弱した状態にある場合はどうなりますか？
quickly become incapacitated and dependent
すぐに無力になり、依存してしまう
What about the topic we're talking about today?
今日話しているテーマについてはどうでしょうか？
that's how
そうやって
let at a very old age
非常に高齢になってから
To avoid such a situation from happening
このような事態が起こらないようにするために
So it's called
それで、それは呼ばれます
such a state of vitality
そのような活力のある状態
Then I just took this one
それから私はこれを撮っただけです
Let me show you that there is a line in this picture
この写真に線があることを見せてください
That's when you say it's because of various reasons
それは色々な理由があるからだと言うのですが、
when young
若い頃
not taking good care of your body
自分の体をよく世話していない
has entered a state of weakness
衰弱状態に入った
can you still reply
まだ返信できますか
actually it is possible
実際にそれは可能です
which means you can still work hard
つまり、まだ頑張れるということです
let this one of yours
これをあなたのものにしましょう
This function curve comes back up
この関数曲線は元に戻ります
So it's definitely a possible situation
だからそれは間違いなく起こり得る状況です
So we have bodies now
それで私たちは今肉体を持っています
Don't be discouraged by those who rub a little
ちょっとこする人も落胆しないでください
can be used in some ways
いくつかの方法で使用できます
Lifestyle Ways to Get You Back
ライフスタイルで自分を取り戻す方法
Then you walk in a
それからあなたは中を歩きます
Very good for a healthy one on the road
外出中の健康な人にとっては非常に良い
Well, what I just talked about is
さて、私が今話したのは、
because we talk about vitality
私たちは活力について話しているので
So we're talking about its inverse
だから私たちはその逆について話しているのです
weak
衰弱
Frailty and sarcopenia are two sides of the same coin
フレイルとサルコペニアは表裏の関係にある
I think many of you have heard of sarcopenia
サルコペニアという言葉を聞いたことがある方も多いと思います
basically means
基本的に意味するのは
Sarcopenia is when your body
サルコペニアはあなたの体が
This muscle mass gradually decreases
この筋肉量は徐々に減少していきます
reduce
減少
But it may not have reached a critical point
でもまだ臨界点には達していないかもしれない
so you can function normally
それであなたは正常に機能することができます
But in one case
しかし、あるケースでは
less muscle mass
筋肉量が少ない
Plus the quality of the muscle
筋肉の質もプラス
if bad again
またダメなら
so-called debility
いわゆる衰弱
Frailty is often closely related to chronic disease
フレイルは慢性疾患と密接に関係していることが多い
I just talked about frailty and disability
フレイルと障害についてお話しました
may cause disability
障害を引き起こす可能性があります
Then if we look at some statistics
次に、いくつかの統計を見てみると
If we look at the weakened group
弱体化したグループを見てみると
Half of him has various so-called chronic diseases
彼の半分はさまざまないわゆる慢性疾患を抱えています
As mentioned by our vice president just now, cardiovascular diseases and diabetes
先ほど副社長からもお話がありましたが、心血管疾患と糖尿病
various diseases
さまざまな病気
Then these diseases will indeed cause the debility to occur earlier
そうすれば、これらの病気は確かに衰弱をより早く引き起こすでしょう
One-fifth of the feeble
弱者の5分の1
One in five is also paired with disabilities and comorbidities
5人に1人は障害や併存疾患を抱えている
About 6% are disabled but have no comorbidities
約6%は障害はあるが併存疾患はない
Almost one in four people with only frailty alone
ほぼ4人に1人が虚弱性のみを抱えている
this is the situation
これは事実です
So we can see that these conditions exist at the same time
したがって、これらの条件が同時に存在することがわかります
Then I will use the slide below to talk to you
それでは、下のスライドを使ってお話しさせていただきます
the health of the elderly
高齢者の健康
What kind of problems do the elderly face?
高齢者はどのような問題に直面しているのでしょうか？
It's not just the old people we often hear
よく聞くのは老人だけではありません
Have high blood pressure, diabetes, hyperlipidemia, heart disease, stroke
高血圧、糖尿病、高脂血症、心臓病、脳卒中などがある
Uh, these are not just one question.
まあ、これらはそのような質問だけではありません。
Let me explain to you from this diagram
この図から説明していきます
each of us will age
私たち一人一人は老いていきます
even if you don't have any disease
たとえ病気がなくても
You too are on an aging path
あなたも老化の道を進んでいます
Possibly due to physical damage from some free machines
おそらく一部の無料マシンによる物理的損傷が原因であると考えられます
cell aging etc.
細胞の老化など
Some DNA damage will lead to this aging path
一部の DNA 損傷はこの老化経路につながります
But this aging process if you have some
しかし、この老化プロセスがいくつかある場合、
the disease i just mentioned
さっき言った病気
it's going to be faster
もっと速くなります
What about the state of aging?
老化の状態はどうでしょうか？
uh when it happens
ああ、それが起こったら
Our bodies may be in a long-term
私たちの体は長期にわたる可能性があります
a low-grade inflammatory state
軽度の炎症状態
With some endocrine wet strips and metabolic changes
内分泌の湿潤ストリップと代謝の変化を伴う
uh lead to
ああ、つながる
But gradually, some phenomena will occur
しかし、徐々に、いくつかの現象が発生します
I just talked about frailty
先ほどフレイルについてお話しました
But before this debility
しかし、この衰弱の前に
Maybe something like these
たぶんこれらのようなもの
In fact, there are also some mental symptoms
実は精神的な症状もあります
easy to say
言うのはたやすい
melancholy forget
憂鬱で忘れ去られた
Some anemia, lack of strength
若干の貧血、エネルギー不足
The problem with swallowing flames
炎を飲み込む問題
wet urine
濡れた尿
or insomnia, malnutrition
あるいは不眠症、栄養失調
Sarcopenia
サルコペニア
often as i just said
先ほど言ったようによくある
because of disease
病気のせいで
such a person in such a state
そんな人がこんな状態に
often used a lot of drugs
多くの薬物を使用することが多い
people who take a lot of drugs
大量の薬を服用している人
What about these risk factors?
これらの危険因子についてはどうでしょうか?
Later it will show a
後で表示されます
debilitating condition
衰弱状態
is that there will be several aspects
いくつかの側面があるということです
like sudden weight loss
突然の体重減少のような
So we observed an old man
そこで私たちはある老人を観察しました
Suddenly we said that it is not good to be too fat
突然太りすぎるのは良くないと言いました
But if you are already fat
しかし、すでに太っている場合は、
If you observe a fat old man
太った老人を観察していたら
suddenly lost weight
急に体重が減った
that's not a good
それは良くない
if he is not there
彼がそこにいないなら
It seems to be eating healthy
健康的に食べているようです
or love sports
またはスポーツが好き
Sudden weight loss is a warning sign
急激な体重減少は危険信号です
It's a warning sign of weakness
それは弱さの警告サインです
sudden weight loss
突然の体重減少
Then he often feels exhausted
それから彼はしばしば疲れを感じます
His hand grip is not strong enough
彼の手の握力は十分に強くありません
I have no strength to hold things
物を掴む力がない
It's natural that I don't want to go out.
外に出たくないのは当然です。
I used to take a walk, but now I don't take a walk anymore.
以前は散歩していましたが、今は散歩しません。
I don't do some things normally
普段はやらないこともある
Walking, the speed is getting slower and slower
歩く速度がどんどん遅くなる
These phenomena are the so-called swerving
こういった現象はいわゆる蛇行現象です
when this happens right after
直後にこれが起こったとき
susceptible to injury and infection
怪我や感染症にかかりやすい
easy to fall
落ちやすい
that leads to disability and death
それは障害や死につながる
So basically it's an old you health issue
つまり、基本的には高齢者の健康上の問題です
so i'm talking about
だから私が話しているのは
It's really full of problems behind
背後には本当に問題がいっぱいです
But I think people in their fifties and sixties
でも50代、60代の方だと思います
should start to understand the problem
問題を理解し始めるはずだ
Even people in their thirties and forties
30代、40代の方でも
you can also follow
フォローすることもできます
You can also help the elderly in your own home
ご自宅でもお年寄りのお手伝いができます
So the phenomenon just now
それで今の現象は
In fact, it is what I just called the elderly positive group
実際、彼らは私が先ほど高齢者陽性グループと呼んだものです。
Here's what I just said
これが私が今言ったことです
It broadly refers to health problems that are common among the elderly
高齢者によく見られる健康上の問題を広く指します。
The problem with these forces
これらの力の問題
Weakness Forgetfulness Depression Malnutrition
衰弱 物忘れ うつ病 栄養失調
cognitive function problems
認知機能の問題
urinary incontinence etc incontinence
尿失禁などの失禁
And even some pain in the window
そして窓に多少の痛みさえも
these are included
これらは含まれています
But we just talked about these phenomena
しかし、私たちはこれらの現象について話したばかりです
It means that of course there are some
もちろんそういうものもあるということです
Not necessarily only for the elderly
必ずしも高齢者だけが対象というわけではない
So do this for the elderly
だから、高齢者のためにこれをしてください
When discussing geriatric syndrome
老年症候群について話すとき
We will focus more on frailty
フレイルにもっと焦点を当てていきます
Sarcopenia and falls
サルコペニアと転倒
This is the three persons who are the three sides of the same one
これは同じものの三面である三人です
Dementia is a little different
また、認知症は少し異なります
just a little bit different
少しだけ違う
This is a system of muscles and balance
これは筋肉とバランスのシステムです
This dementia is a direction of our brain brand
この認知症は私たちの脳ブランドの方向性です
geriatric syndrome
老人症候群
We found a strong correlation with nutritional status privacy patterns
栄養状態とプライバシーのパターンとの強い相関関係が判明
So what I'm going to talk about today is
それで、今日私が話そうとしていることは、
Some of our international literature
私たちの国際文学の一部
Some information we have seen and our Taiwan
私たちが見てきたいくつかの情報と私たちの台湾
Especially the research done by our sustainable project
特に私たちの持続可能なプロジェクトによって行われた研究
first let me tell you
まず言っておきます
Papers we have published in 2017
2017年に出版した論文
We use Taiwan's Nutritional Health Survey
台湾の栄養健康調査を使用しています
Found that we Taiwan's elderly over 65 years old
私たち台湾の65歳以上の高齢者であることを発見しました
The so-called robust in the middle is completely fine
いわゆる真ん中の堅牢さは全く問題ありません
40% without any signs of weakness
40% 衰弱の兆候なし
7.8% over the age of 65 are already frail
65 歳以上の 7.8% はすでに虚弱である
What is weakness?
弱さとは何でしょうか？
The five aspects I just talked about
今お話しした5つの側面
If there are three such phenomena in the middle
このような現象が真ん中に3つある場合
so-called weakness
いわゆる弱さ
What is it?
それは何ですか？
walking too slowly
歩くのが遅すぎる
weight loss
減量
always feel tired
いつも疲れを感じている
reduced physical activity
身体活動の減少
I don't have the strength and don't want to go out to do it
体力がないので外に出たくない
three is called weakness
３つは弱さという
then one or two words
それから一言か二言
pre-frailty
プレフレイル
In fact, people over the age of 65
実は65歳以上の人は
we look like this
私たちはこう見えます
Sixty percent already have
60％はすでに持っています
A phenomenon of more than one weakening
複数が弱体化する現象
Then I will
それなら私はそうします
OK, what if I get here?
OK、ここに着いたらどうする？
I'm just telling you
ただ言っているだけです
It's one of my main axes today
それが今の私の主軸の一つです
geriatric syndrome
老人症候群
Then I will talk about the following
それでは次のことについてお話します
as the body ages
体が老化するにつれて
What kind of situation is the change with the body
体の変化はどのような状況ですか
Then this might get some younger people thinking
そうなると、若い人たちもこう思うかもしれない
I will
私はこれから
That is to say, how do we develop as human beings?
つまり、人間としてどのように成長していくのかということです。
It will develop into the weakened state I just mentioned
先ほど述べた弱体化状態に発展します。
let's take a look
見てみましょう
the body mass index
肥満指数
Both waist circumference and waist circumference are well-known indicators of obesity
腹囲と胴囲はどちらも肥満のよく知られた指標です
That obesity indicator
その肥満指標
On the left is body mass index
左側はBMIです
We all know the weight
重さはみんな知ってるよ
In addition to height
身長に加えて
divide twice
2回に分ける
Or divide by the square of the height
または高さの二乗で割ります
In our impression
私たちの印象では
That is, whether people have followed from the student days
つまり学生時代から続けているかどうか
just getting fatter
太るだけ
Is it in our impression?
それは私たちの印象にあるのでしょうか？
Look at the books in the nutrition and health survey
栄養と健康に関する調査の本を見てください
We see ages from 19 to 44 to middle age 45 to 64
19歳から44歳から中年層の45歳から64歳までの年齢層がいます。
Inside this frame are the elderly
この枠の中には高齢者がいます
He sure is only going to get better and better
彼は確かにますます良くなるばかりだ
But after entering the age of 65
しかし65歳を超えてからは
In men, he actually falls down
男性の場合、彼は実際に倒れます
After the age of 65, the weight will come down
65歳を過ぎると体重は減ります
Many people may be very happy when this comes down
これが実現すると多くの人はとても喜ぶかもしれません
but it's not
しかしそうではありません
shouldn't be too happy
あまり幸せになってはいけません
you should pay attention
注意を払うべきです
because it might be a
かもしれないから
the mass of your body
あなたの体の質量
some parts have been reduced
一部の部分が削減されました
that's what it means
それが意味です
the same waist
同じウエスト
You see the waist was thinner when you were young
若い頃はウエストが細かったのがわかります
getting thicker
厚くなる
At the age of 65 to 69
65歳から69歳まで
still in the upper body
まだ上半身に
But after the age of 70, it will come down
でも70歳を過ぎると下がるよ
The man saw a phenomenon
男はある現象を見た
Then women are different
それなら女性は違います
women age
女性の年齢
So the old lady is very obedient when she arrives.
それで、老婦人は到着すると非常に従順です。
This is a phenomenon in Taiwan
これは台湾での現象です
But will women go through this process later?
しかし、女性は後にこのプロセスを経験するのでしょうか？
because we investigate
私たちが調査するから
when doing this national
これを全国的にやるときは
but the very old are less
しかし、超高齢者は少ない
So there is no way to watch it after this 80
80以降は見る方法がないので
In fact, when women are old
実は、女性は歳をとると、
Maybe after 90s
たぶん90年代以降
They are also weight will BMI physical acceleration
また、体重とBMI、身体加速度も関係します。
will come down
降りてくるでしょう
So a drop like this is a sign of aging
つまり、このような低下は老化の兆候です
It's a sign of geriatric syndrome
それは老人症候群の兆候です
Women are on this picture also see the upper
この写真に女性が写っていますが、上部もご覧ください
Because our last grouping is 80 years old
私たちの最後のグループは80歳なので
It also showed a rapid loss of body mass in women
女性の体重が急速に減少することも示された
is later than men
男性より遅いです
Men are earlier
男のほうが早いよ
There is such a phenomenon
そんな現象あるんですね
So let's look at body mass index
それではBMIを見てみましょう
with our bones in the middle
私たちの骨が真ん中にある
have our muscles
私たちの筋肉を持っています
and our fat all put together
私たちの脂肪をすべて合わせて
It is not easy to make an understanding
理解するのは簡単ではない
What about our muscles?
私たちの筋肉はどうでしょうか？
That is, the blue above is male
上の青いのが雄です
the following is female
以下は女性です
If our men are young people from 19 to 44 years old
当社の男性が19歳から44歳までの若者の場合
What about over 80 years old?
80歳を超えたらどうでしょうか？
Muscle is 6 kg less
筋肉が6kg減った
The current situation of Taiwanese
台湾人の現状
Then the female is less than 2.2 kg
するとメスは2.2kg未満
that debilitating condition
その衰弱状態
Appearing here is the weakness I just mentioned.
ここに先ほど述べた弱点が現れます。
Early asthenia and no signs of asthenia
初期の無力症および無力症の兆候なし
you can see weak people
弱い人が見える
How about compared to people who are not weak?
弱くない人と比べたらどうでしょうか？
It's 6kg short
6kg足りない
There are old people here
ここには老人がいる
because in young people
なぜなら若者の中には
We didn't do his debilitating assessment
私たちは彼の衰弱を招く評価をしませんでした
such a young woman
あんな若い女性
For older women, the difference is 1.5 kg
高齢女性の場合、その差は1.5kg
but i want to emphasize
しかし強調したいのは
just let everybody see us from this young adult
この若い大人からの私たちをみんなに見てもらいましょう
to old age
老後へ
You see our muscular men lose 6kg
筋肉質の男性が 6kg 痩せているのがわかりますね
Women lost 2.2 kg
女性は2.2kg減量
Of course women and men at the beginning
もちろん最初は女性も男性も
It's about 20kg short
20kgくらい足りない
men and women have big muscles
男性も女性も大きな筋肉を持っています
So women often have muscle soreness, these things
女性は筋肉痛になることが多いのですが、
because women have less muscle, that's one reason
女性は筋肉が少ないので、それが理由の1つです
The other thing is hemoglobin, which is an indicator of normal blood.
もう1つはヘモグロビンで、これは血液が正常であることを示す指標です。
We can see males as young adults versus this middle aged
男性はこの中年者であるのに対し、若い成人であると見ることができます。
His hemoglobin is very high, maintaining around 15
彼のヘモグロビンは非常に高く、約15を維持しています
But as soon as he enters old age he declines
しかし老年期に入るとすぐに衰退する
Therefore, it is very difficult for men to level blood. Men only have two points to level blood.
そのため、男性が血液を平らにするのは非常に難しく、男性が血液を平らにするポイントはたったの2つだけです。
One is around the age of 12 when he grows very fast he will flat blood
1人は12歳くらいで、成長が非常に早く、血液を平らにするでしょう
Then when they grow into adults, men will no longer have flat blood
そして大人になると、男性は平らな血を持たなくなります
It wasn't until he was old that he started to have flat blood.
彼が平らな血を持つようになったのは、彼が年をとってからでした。
Well women are not, women are a problem at a young age because of the need to reproduce
女性はそうではありません、女性は生殖の必要性があるため、若い年齢では問題があります
Therefore, when women are young, their hemoglobin is only a little over 12
したがって、女性が若いときのヘモグロビンは 12 を少し超える程度です。
After menopause, women's hemoglobin will rise
女性は閉経するとヘモグロビンが増加します
I no longer feel dizzy and lack of energy.
めまいもエネルギーもなくなりました
But after the sixties
しかし60年代以降
will also slowly decline a little bit
またゆっくりと少しずつ減っていくでしょう
This range is very small
この範囲は非常に小さいです
But it is a significant drop
しかし大幅な下落です
So what does this tell us about the problem?
では、このことから問題について何がわかるでしょうか?
It's about energy
それはエネルギーについてです
means no strength or anything
力も何もないという意味
This is related to the aspect of anemia
これは貧血と関係があります
also have some relationship
何らかの関係もある
So there's this one
それで、これがあります
A phenomenon we should pay attention to
私たちが注目すべき現象
The other one is lung function
もう一つは肺機能です
inhalation of this oxygen
この酸素を吸入することで
Inhalation is the same as we often use
吸入は私たちがよく使うものと同じです
The so-called maximal forced expiratory volume
いわゆる最大努力呼気量
forced expiratory volume in the first second
最初の1秒間の努力呼気量
Then this is related to a
それから、これは
spirometry problems
肺活量的問題
then this is a
それならこれは
This is the so-called trachea
いわゆる気管です
A question on Tongtong
トントンについて質問です
you can see that is to say
つまりそれはわかります
in young adults
若者の中で
He has a lung capacity of four liters
彼の肺活量は4リットルです
In the eighties, there are two liters left
80年代には残り2リットル
dropped by half
半分に減った
This is also quite influential
これもかなり影響力あるよ
Women drop from 3 liters to 1.5 liters
女性は3リットルから1.5リットルに減る
Then this forced expiratory volume in the first second
次に、最初の 1 秒間の努力呼気量
also dropped a lot
もたくさん落ちた
If some prospective data
何らかの見込みデータがあれば
you can see that is to say
つまりそれはわかります
This waste activity volume and this exhalation volume in the first second
最初の1秒間のこの老廃物活動量とこの呼気量
When the degree of a person's weakness
人の弱さの程度が
are very relevant
非常に関連性があります
It is also related to the amount of a person's muscles.
それはその人の筋肉の量にも関係します。
Of course, this causal relationship is difficult to say
もちろん、この因果関係は何とも言えませんが、
Is it because your muscles are lacking
筋肉が足りないからですか？
so your breath
だからあなたの息
You can't have such a large amount of waste
そんなに大量のゴミはありえない
It should be said that it may be the cause of the muscles
それは筋肉のせいかもしれないと言うべきです
muscular cause
筋肉の原因
so this
したがって、この
one theory is this
一説はこれです
exercise your muscles
筋肉を鍛える
Also includes this waste activity
この廃棄活動も含まれます
Because the muscles of the whole body and the transverse lattice
全身の筋肉と横格子があるので、
These muscles are all related
これらの筋肉はすべて関連しています
This is also weak
これも弱い
is very closely related
非常に密接に関係している
In addition, it is often used to measure
また、測定にもよく使われます。
It is the five aspects I just mentioned
それが今お話しした5つの側面です
It's Linda Freed's five facets
それはリンダ・フリードの5つの側面です
One is walking speed and the other is lying force
1 つは歩行速度、もう 1 つは横たわる力です
You can see this green is male
この緑は雄であることがわかります
gray is female descended
灰色は女性の子孫です
This is because we only test the elderly
高齢者だけを検査しているからです
So from the age of 65 to the age of 80, it has dropped by 1.4
つまり、65歳から80歳までに1.4減少したことになります。
down by 1.3
1.3減少
What about this power?
この力はどうでしょうか？
This place is in kilograms
ここはキログラム単位です
Lost 8.6kg from 60s to 80s
60代から80代にかけて8.6kg減量
Female dropped 4.2kg
女性は4.2kg減
So we look at a drop like this
このようなドロップを見てみましょう
so these are
それで、これらは
The parameters I just talked about
先ほど話したパラメータ
Everyone can pay attention
誰もが注目できる
just like i used to
私が以前のように
because I do nutritional surveys
栄養調査をしているので
Once I asked someone from my team to help me
かつてチームの誰かに助けを求めたことがあります
i think i'm in good health
私は健康だと思う
Measured my waste activity
私の老廃物活動を測定しました
They said teacher, your amount of wasted work is below average
先生、あなたの無駄な仕事の量は平均以下だよって言われました
i was startled
私はびっくりした
I said it turned out that my waste activity
私の無駄遣いが判明したと言いました
That part of me might need some work out too
私のその部分もトレーニングが必要かもしれません
Then there is also the reclining force that can be measured.
それから、測定可能なリクライニング力もあります。
Hemoglobin can also be measured
ヘモグロビンも測定可能
These are now with some tapering
これらは現在、若干の先細りになっています
start gradually incorporating these items
これらのアイテムを徐々に取り入れていきます
so everyone can understand
誰もが理解できるように
A health condition of my own
私自身の健康状態
The development of this course of fear is generally considered to be
この恐怖の進行は一般に次のように考えられています。
related to genetic and environmental factors
遺伝的および環境的要因に関連する
The other common interaction of these factors
これらの要因のその他の一般的な相互作用
damage some cells in our body
私たちの体の一部の細胞にダメージを与える
or a lesion at some molecular level
または何らかの分子レベルでの病変
This damage will affect some functional decline of multiple system organs
この損傷は複数の臓器の機能低下に影響を及ぼします。
Including brain, endocrine, immune, muscle, heart, blood vessel, breathing, kidney, etc.
脳、内分泌、免疫、筋肉、心臓、血管、呼吸、腎臓などが含まれます。
I just mentioned things like breathing, muscles
先ほど呼吸や筋肉などについて触れました
after this drop
この下落の後
Without proper nutrition such a lifestyle
適切な栄養がなければ、そのようなライフスタイル
and use proper physical activity to maintain your body's muscles
体の筋肉を維持するために適切な身体活動をしましょう
and cell function
そして細胞機能
It is easy to develop symptoms of dread
恐怖の症状が出やすい
This is what I just mentioned when something unexpected happens
これは、予期せぬことが起こったときに先ほど言ったものです
metabolic syndrome
メタボリック・シンドローム
Next, I will use this picture again.
次に、この写真をもう一度使用します。
let me tell you about this
これについてお話しさせてください
The vicious cycle of aging and disease
老化と病気の悪循環
a state
状態
so everyone can understand
誰もが理解できるように
Sometimes we also observe
時々観察することもあります
some changes in your body
あなたの体に何らかの変化が
you may know
あなたは知っているかもしれません
We are all aging
私たちは皆老化しています
and there may be some diseases
そして何かの病気の可能性もあります
sorry this is in english
ごめんなさい、これは英語です
This is really hard to change to Chinese
これを中国語に変えるのは本当に難しいです
So I will speak clearly when I speak
だから話すときははっきりと話すようにします
So in the process
それでその過程で
Did we just talk about it
それについて話したばかりですか
our muscles will decrease
私たちの筋肉は減少します
What about when we lose muscle?
筋肉が減るとどうなるでしょうか？
It will happen that a phenomenon is
という現象が起こります
My so-called basal metabolic rate drops
いわゆる基礎代謝量が低下します
Because muscles are very energy-consuming
筋肉は非常にエネルギーを消費するので、
when you lose muscle now
今筋肉が減ったら
you don't need so much energy
そんなにエネルギーは必要ありません
your metabolic rate drops
代謝率が低下します
What about after a drop?
ドロップ後はどうでしょうか？
your need your this
あなたにはこれが必要です
You need to burn fewer calories
消費カロリーを減らす必要がある
It means you are a person with less muscle
つまり筋肉が少ない人ということになります
You just sleep over there and you drain energy
ただそこで寝ているだけでエネルギーを消耗してしまう
So in this case the words
したがって、この場合の言葉は、
your appetite may be affected
食欲に影響が出る可能性があります
You don't need so many calories
そんなにカロリーは必要ありません
your appetite is affected
あなたの食欲は影響を受けます
Did you start not wanting to eat?
食べたくなくなり始めましたか？
you don't want to eat after
その後は食べたくないですか
Just slowly this nutrient
この栄養素をゆっくりと
less will come in
入ってくることは少なくなります
The cycle will continue after less
サイクルはその後も継続します
the so-called negative calorie balance
いわゆるマイナスカロリー収支
After negative caloric balance
カロリーバランスがマイナスになった後
after your calorie loss
カロリーを減らした後
do you have less muscle
筋肉が少ないですか
you enter a vicious cycle
悪循環に陥ってしまいます
The part that can't move
動かせない部分
is to say
言うことです
when you have less muscle
筋肉が少ないとき
you have no strength
あなたには力がありません
Then your VO2
次に、VO2
is your oxygen
あなたの酸素は何ですか
VO2 will drop
VO2が下がります
The amount of oxygen you can breathe in drops
吸い込める酸素の量が減ってしまう
like this case
このケースのように
you walk slower
あなたはもっとゆっくり歩きます
when you walk slowly
ゆっくり歩くとき
your activity
あなたの活動
you don't want to go out
外出したくないのですか
So you're less active again
それでまた活動性が下がったね
Then further reduce
その後さらに減らす
caloric needs
必要なカロリー
eat less calories
カロリーを減らして食べる
what about less
少ないのはどうですか
Nutrients come in less
摂取できる栄養素が少なくなる
After that, you will have less energy
その後はエネルギーが少なくなります
so it's a vicious cycle
だから悪循環だよ
So when we understand such a situation
ですから、そのような状況を理解すると、
If you find out that it is the old man in the family
家族のおじさんだとわかったら
when there is such a situation
そのような状況があるとき
you have to break it
それを壊さなければなりません
Your cycle can be interrupted
サイクルが中断される可能性があります
you just have to give it some broken links
壊れたリンクをいくつか追加するだけです
Start with the simpler of course
もちろん簡単なものから始めてください
So exercise and diet are closely related
つまり、運動と食事は密接に関係しているのです
Although I am talking about diet today
今日はダイエットの話ですが
But exercise is essential
でも運動は欠かせない
But because there are more sports information
でもスポーツ情報が多いので
Everyone knows how to exercise
誰もが運動方法を知っています
So today I just focus on
だから今日はただそれに焦点を当てます
I am more professional this is
私はよりプロフェッショナルです、これは
part of nutrition
栄養の一部
So what I'm going to say is
それで、私が言いたいのは、
This vicious cycle can be broken
この悪循環は断ち切ることができる
that may have to wait until the end to ask the question
質問するには最後まで待たなければならないかもしれません
we will continue
私たちは続けます
So when I talk about this side now
だから今、こちら側の話をすると
I'll start talking to you
あなたと話し始めます
besides sports
スポーツ以外にも
This exercise is definitely to do
この練習は必ずやるべきです
and in motion
そして動いている
There are many tricks, there are many faces
たくさんのトリックがあり、たくさんの顔がある
All kinds of different sports we don't mention today
今日は言及しなかったあらゆる種類のスポーツ
Let's talk about it later
それについては後で話しましょう
Then I will start talking about it today. Good with exercise.
それでは今日はその話をしていきますが、運動は得意です。
then how do we eat
じゃあどうやって食べるか
Only then can this phenomenon
そうして初めてこの現象が起こります
able to make a reply
返事ができる
then let me tell you first
それなら最初に言っておきます
is of course we have to take a look
もちろん見てみる必要があります
current scientific literature
現在の科学文献
The current scientific literature is debilitated in this
現在の科学文献はこの点で弱体化している
What about the little part?
小さな部分はどうですか？
Basically most of them are talking
基本的にはほとんどが喋ってます
protein
タンパク質
that's ok i can say that
大丈夫、それは言えます
Whether transverse or forward
横向きでも前向きでも
That is, you may not know the term
つまり、この用語を知らないかもしれません
but it doesn't matter
でもそれは関係ない
or some interventional experimental research
または介入的な実験研究
Both have supported protein and frailty
どちらもタンパク質と虚弱性をサポートしています
is negatively correlated
負の相関がある
mean to say
言う意味
you eat more protein
あなたはより多くのタンパク質を食べます
you won't be weak easily
あなたは簡単には弱くなりません
you eat less protein
タンパク質の摂取量が減ります
you are more likely to weaken
あなたは弱くなる可能性が高くなります
This is especially about the elderly
これは特に高齢者についてです
so older people
とても年上の人たち
That is to say, this protein cannot be ignored
つまり、このタンパク質は無視できません
I remember two days ago I was with a colleague
2日前に同僚と一緒にいたことを覚えています
so-called advanced intellectuals
いわゆる高度な知識人
We all happened to be vegetarians.
私たちはたまたまベジタリアンでした。
Be vegetarian because when we eat out
外食するときはベジタリアンになりましょう
I think vegetarian bento is safer
ベジタリアン弁当の方が安全だと思う
Because its oil will not be a bad oil
そのオイルは悪いオイルではないので
But this vegetarian bento happens to be inside
でも、たまたまこのベジタリアン弁当が入っていたんです
It's all vegetables without any protein
たんぱく質を含まないすべて野菜です
so i told the restaurant
それでレストランに言いました
can we have some protein
プロテインを飲んでもいいですか
Then my colleague said
すると同僚が言いました
no no no no protein
いやいやいやプロテイン
I said why
理由を言いました
He said the burden of winning is too heavy
勝つことの負担が重すぎると彼は言った
Then I tell him it's important
それから私は彼にそれが重要だと言います
He said it was especially important for the elderly
彼はそれが高齢者にとって特に重要だと言いました
Then my colleague immediately told me that
すると同僚がすぐにこう言いました。
I think old people just shouldn't eat too much protein
老人はたんぱく質をあまり食べるべきではないと思う
The burden of victory is too heavy
勝利の重荷は重すぎる
Then of course I'm not good
それならもちろん私はダメです
but i know
しかし私は知っている
This means that many people have such a concept
そういう概念を持っている人が多いということです
That is to say, the elderly should not eat too much protein
つまり、高齢者はタンパク質を過剰に摂取すべきではありません
May be physically taxing
肉体的に負担がかかる可能性がある
Then I want to tell you that
それから私はあなたにそれを言いたいです
The current scientific literature is
現在の科学文献は、
Supports the release of protein and herbal medicines Interrelated
タンパク質と生薬の放出をサポート 相互に関連
Then these studies
それから、これらの研究は
I have no way to talk to you today
今日はあなたと話す機会がない
It's probably an egg balancing study
おそらく卵のバランスの研究です
that is, discussing a person
つまり、人について議論することです
how much protein do i give it
どのくらいの量のプロテインを与えればよいですか
and see how much it excretes
そしてどれだけ排泄されるかを見てください
Which point will reach the balance
どの点でバランスが取れるのか
Most of these studies
これらの研究のほとんどは
Of course there are new ways
もちろん新しいやり方もあるよ
use this stable
この安定版を使用してください
Isotopes of ISO TOG
ISO TOG的同位素
Add a label to that amino acid and eat it
そのアミノ酸にラベルを付けて食べる
Then look in the middle of the exhaled air
次に、吐き出された空気の真ん中を見てください。
how much of this
これはいくらですか
These isotopes use this method
これらの同位体はこの方法を使用します
many ways to make
たくさんの作り方
Well, we don't have such research in Taiwan at all.
そうですね、台湾ではそのような研究は全くありません。
So in order to understand Taiwanese
台湾語を理解するには
How much protein should I eat?
タンパク質はどのくらい摂取すればよいですか?
We used another method
別の方法を使用しました
This method is to say
この方法はつまり、
AI for Nutrients
栄養素のための AI
AI is the so-called appropriate intake
AIはいわゆる適正摂取です
this is a method
これは方法です
This method is acceptable in nutrition
この方法は栄養学の分野で受け入れられます
it means
その意味は
If you do not have the appropriate data
適切なデータがない場合
you just evaluate that
あなたはそれを評価するだけです
How much do those people who have no problem at all eat?
全く問題ない人はどれくらい食べているのでしょうか？
Because we do not have such research in Taiwan
台湾ではそのような研究が行われていないため、
Then these researches are being done by several groups around the world
これらの研究は世界中のいくつかのグループによって行われています
The egg balance study I just talked about
先ほどお話しした卵バランス研究
So we use Taiwan from 2014 to 2017
したがって、2014 年から 2017 年までは台湾を使用します。
This nutritional data in 2017
この栄養データは2017年のものです
let's do the math
計算してみましょう
We just divide the elderly into
高齢者を次のように分けるだけです
Frailty Non-frailty Early stage of frailty and frailty
フレイル ノンフレイル フレイルおよびフレイルの初期段階
Let's see, everyone just look at the data on the right.
そうですね、皆さん右側のデータを見てください。
Here is the number of people doing statistics
これは統計を行っている人の数です
Then the most important thing for us to see is that there is no problem.
そして、私たちにとって最も重要なことは、問題がないことです。
These elderly people without debilitating diseases
衰弱性疾患のないこれらの高齢者
what is his protein intake
彼のタンパク質摂取量はどれくらいですか
We see that it is 1.2 grams per kilogram of body weight
体重1キログラムあたり1.2グラムであることがわかります
1.21 male female is 1.22
男性は1.21、女性は1.22
this is a median
これは中央値です
Of course, this is a concept of our statistics
もちろん、これは私たちの統計の概念です
That means I don't use averages
つまり、平均値は使用しないということです
instead of the median
中央値の代わりに
what does the median mean
中央値は何を意味しますか
is the most people
が一番多いです
The most lack of people here
ここが一番人が少ない
These people in the middle are all ingesting this amount
真ん中の人たちは全員この量を摂取しています
Then we dare not use the average
したがって、あえて平均値を使用しません。
Why? Because people eat protein and some people eat a lot
なぜかというと、人々はたんぱく質を摂取しており、たくさん食べる人もいるからです。
Incredibly many
信じられないほどたくさん
So once you average down, the average value will be skewed.
したがって、平均値を下げると、平均値が歪んでしまいます。
So we use the median
したがって、中央値を使用します
We can see debilitated people who weigh a kilogram a day
1日の体重が1キロもある衰弱した人々を目にすることができます
eat less than a gram
1グラム未満しか食べない
Pre-failure is centered
事前障害が中心にあります
Then this number may not mean anything to you
そうすると、この数字はあなたにとって何の意味もないかもしれません
Maybe you see this number and think its nothing
この数字を見て、何もないと思うかもしれません
but i want to tell you
でも、あなたに言いたいのです
Globally International Recommendations for Protein
世界的にプロテインに関する国際的な推奨事項
almost all have a number
ほぼ全員に番号が付いています
That number is 1.2
その数字は1.2です
Doesn't matter if it's Canadian or EU people
カナダ人か欧州連合の人かは関係ありません
he basically said
彼は基本的に言った
An old man needs to eat 1.2 grams per kilogram of body weight a day
老人は一日に体重1キログラム当たり1.2グラムを食べる必要がある
Then this 1.2 grams is meaningless to everyone
そうすると、この1.2グラムは誰にとっても意味がありません。
I don't know how much 1.2 grams is
1.2グラムが何グラムなのか分からない
I'll talk to you later
また話そう
you can eat like this
このように食べることができます
So this 1.2 grams is a magic trick
つまり、この 1.2 グラムは魔法のトリックなのです
Same as Magic Number
マジックナンバーと同じ
But now there are actually some other children
でも今は実際には他にも子供たちがいます
yes
はい
Most people are like this, but if you are in a
ほとんどの人がそうなのですが、もしあなたがそのような状況に陥っているなら、
For example, the state of illness, the state of lying down for a long time
例えば、病気の状態、長時間横になっている状態など。
In fact, your body's response to protein
実際、タンパク質に対する体の反応は
Utilization is poor and you have to add more
使用率が低いため、さらに追加する必要があります
Can be increased to 1.4
1.4まで増やすことができます
Even some people 1.6 can have such a guide
1.6 の人でもそのようなガイドを持つことができます
But one thing I'm happy to say is that
でも一つだけ嬉しい事があるんです
We use this AI's orphan algorithm
このAIの孤立アルゴリズムを使用しています
The figures obtained in Taiwan are similar to those obtained internationally.
台湾で得られた数値は国際的に得られた数値と類似しています。
Then this data we also
次に、このデータをまた、
It is recommended to go to the National Health Service of our country
我が国の国民保健サービスに行くことをお勧めします
what does that mean
どういう意味ですか
Then I will now test because of such a data
それでは、このようなデータがあるのでテストしてみます
Taiwan
台湾
We all know the advice to the people
私たちは皆、人々へのアドバイスを知っています
Our government promulgated a policy called the American-Japanese Dietary Guidelines
私たちの政府は、日米食事ガイドラインと呼ばれる政策を公布しました。
This American-Japanese Dietary Guide is precisely calculated
この日米の食事ガイドは正確に計算されています
That is, if you keep eating
つまり食べ続けると
All your nutrients will be up to standard
すべての栄養素が基準を満たすようになります
But back then
でもあの頃は
when doing this
これをするとき
No one knows that the body weight of the old man's body is 1.2 grams
老人の体重が1.2グラムであることを誰も知りません
At that time, we used the target of 1.0 instead of 1.2
当時は 1.2 ではなく 1.0 という目標を使用しました。
So now I want to say okay let's check it out
だから今、私は言いたい、分かった、それを見てみましょう
Will everyone be getting enough of what the country recommends?
国が推奨するものを誰もが十分に摂取できるでしょうか？
So in fact, there are some recommended calories for each age group
実際には、各年齢層に推奨カロリーがいくつかあります
Make some suggestions according to the weight and height of our Taiwanese, you see
台湾人の体重と身長に応じていくつかの提案をしてください。
So in fact, the recommendations are very detailed for people aged 19 to 34
実際、推奨事項は 19 歳から 34 歳までの人々に対して非常に詳細に規定されています。
If he eats such 1850 calories
1850カロリーも食べたら
Or he eats 2150 to above
あるいは2150以上食べる
Is his protein enough enough to reach 1 kg 1.2 grams
彼のタンパク質は1kgに達するのに十分ですか1.2グラム
Really boys are enough, 31 to 50 years old
本当は男の子で十分、31歳から50歳まで
It's all OK because even a 71-year-old
71歳の男性でも大丈夫です
If he eats 1650 calories he will be enough
1650カロリー食べれば十分だろう
But we found that if it is on the female side
しかし、それが女性側にある場合は、
From young women he has some people who eat very little
若い女性の中には、ほとんど食べない人もいる
1450 calories only
1450カロリーのみ
In old age, some women in their 70s only eat 1300 calories
高齢になると、70代の女性の中には1300カロリーしか食べない人もいます
Everyone knows that many weight loss diets are 1200 calories
減量ダイエットの多くは1200カロリーであることは誰もが知っています
So Yiqiansans understanding of non-film and television is not far behind
つまり、1,003 人は映画以外のことやテレビもそれほど遅れていないことを理解している
So for those who are older and eat less
したがって、高齢で食べる量が少ない人にとっては、
His protein is not enough
彼のタンパク質は十分ではありません
So here's a thing
それで、ここに問題があります
In fact, there is usually a general rule
実際には、通常、一般的なルールがあります
That is if you eat very little people
それはあなたが食べる人をほんの少ししか食べない場合です
you are prone to malnutrition
あなたは栄養失調になりやすいです
So because in the past everyone was
昔はみんなそうだったから
Have you ever thought about being fat?
あなたは太っていることについて考えたことがありますか？
I think it's better to eat less
食べる量は減らしたほうがいいと思う
But the fact here is that if you eat very little
しかし、ここでの事実は、食べる量が非常に少ない場合、
In old age you are very prone to malnutrition
高齢になると栄養失調になりやすい
If there is not enough protein, it will enter the stage of weakness
たんぱく質が不足すると衰弱期に入ります
So let me mention this to you first.
そこで、最初にこのことをお伝えしておきます。
So now we are talking to the government
それで今私たちは政府と話し合っています
Your dietary advice for people who eat less
食べる量が少ない人への食事アドバイス
to modify
変更する
Otherwise these people may fall into protein deficiency
そうしないと、これらの人々はタンパク質欠乏症に陥る可能性があります
Especially the camp French
特にキャンプフレンチ
Then I will tell you more clearly later.
それでは、後ほど詳しくお話します。
Because of this throughout my speech today
このため、今日の私のスピーチ全体を通して
I just want to say that you don't just listen to some principles
ただ言いたいのは、いくつかの原則に耳を傾けるだけではないということです
You really can make a diagnosis of your own diet
自分の食生活を本当に診断できる
so i'll make it clearer later
だから後ではっきりさせます
OK so now I'm done with protein
さて、これでプロテインは終わりです
That is to say, protein is the most concerned in the world
つまり、タンパク質は世界で最も懸念されているのです。
to address the weakness
弱点に対処するために
Then our Taiwan data
次に台湾のデータ
It seems to be consistent with the international data
国際データと一致しているようです
Then in addition
それからさらに
Frailty is not only related to protein
フレイルはたんぱく質だけが関係しているわけではない
Is it not related to other nutrients?
他の栄養素は関係ないのでしょうか？
We found in the literature
文献で見つけました
I saw that it is related to many trace elements
多くの微量元素に関係していることが分かりました
And it seems that there is a phenomenon that
と言う現象があるようです。
Nutrient deficient items
栄養不足の品目
more words
もっと言葉を
the greater the chance that the person is debilitated
その人が衰弱している可能性が高くなります
that phenomenon
その現象
Actually it's a bit paradoxical
実は少し逆説的です
That is, I see that in the literature, apart from protein
つまり、タンパク質とは別に、文献で次のことがわかります。
The lack of number one
ナンバーワンの欠如
Lack of document number B12 Lack of C
文書番号 B12 の欠落 C の欠落
new lack
新たな不足
have some correlation
何らかの相関関係がある
But this correlation
しかし、この相関関係は
what does he mean
彼はどういう意味ですか
that's hard
それは難しいです
We found information in our Taiwan Nutrition and Health Survey
台湾の栄養健康調査で情報が見つかりました
We use something called the 24-hour recall method
私たちは24時間リコール法と呼ばれるものを使用しています
means meeting someone
誰かに会うという意味
I clearly asked him what he ate 24 hours yesterday
昨日24時間何を食べたかはっきりと尋ねました
Made after accurate quantification by various methods of food model
食品モデルの様々な手法により正確に定量化して作成
I just found out that people with sarcopenia in Taiwan
今知ったのですが、台湾にはサルコペニアの人たちがいるんです。
Low protein number B2B12C
低タンパク質数 B2B12C
Calcium manicure
カルシウムマニキュア
30,000 tails of polyvinyl alcohol are low in fatty acids
30,000 尾にはポリヌクレオチドと非保証脂肪酸が少ない
When we see such a phenomenon
このような現象を見ると
Think from the standpoint of a nutritionist
栄養士の立場で考える
I'd think maybe that's not the case
たぶんそうではないと思うよ
It must be that he ate less.
きっと食べる量が減ったのだろう
so you can see everything
すべてが見えるように
Because it is impossible to say that all of the
全部とは言い切れないので、
it's hard to say
言うのが難しい
So one conjecture might be that
したがって、1 つの推測は次のとおりかもしれません
Is it just eating too little?
ただ食べる量が少ないだけなのでしょうか？
will be such a phenomenon
そういう現象になるだろう
And if we know that these many nutrients
そして、これらの多くの栄養素がわかれば、
If I supplement all these nutrients with vitamins
これらの栄養素をビタミンで補えば
can it be
それはできますか
So we have to clarify
したがって、明確にする必要があります
what kind of reason
どのような理由ですか
So we go one step further
そこで私たちはさらに一歩前進します
let's discuss
話し合いましょう
It's the old man in Taiwan
台湾のおじさんです
If he is debilitated
彼が衰弱している場合
his six categories of food
彼の6つの食べ物カテゴリー
his overall diet
彼の全体的な食事
what is it like
それはどんな感じですか
then let me tell you
それなら教えてあげましょう
This is male data
こちらは男性のデータです
I don't know if this will be a little difficult
ちょっと難しいかもわかりませんが、
but i said slowly
でも私はゆっくりと言いました
means you see this
あなたがこれを見ていることを意味します
Men without debilitating disorders
衰弱性障害のない男性
His average calorie intake is 2170 calories a day
彼の平均摂取カロリーは1日2170カロリーです
But when it comes to debility
しかし、衰弱に関して言えば、
He is 1898 kcal
彼は1898kcalです
So about a 200 calorie difference
約200カロリーの差です
He used to eat less overall
彼は全体的に食べる量が減っていました
In the early stage of frailty, I borrowed from the central
フレイルの初期段階で中央から借りました
that you different heat people
あなたたちは異なる熱を持つ人々であることを
he is different
彼は違う
In fact, the six categories of this proposal
実際、この提案の 6 つのカテゴリーは、
What are the six categories of recommendations?
推奨事項の 6 つのカテゴリとは何ですか?
in fact
実際には
When we generally make dietary advice
私たちが一般的に食事に関するアドバイスをするときは、
Divide food into six categories
食べ物を6つのカテゴリーに分ける
It means that you have to eat these six categories
この6つのカテゴリーを食べなければならないということです
these foods
これらの食べ物
And if you eat all of these six categories of food in the amount I suggest you
そして、これら 6 つのカテゴリーの食品をすべて、私が提案する量で食べるなら、
You don't have to worry, you have enough nutrients
心配する必要はありません、栄養は十分にあります
The teacher usually recommends that
先生がよく勧めるのは、
What about when your calories are low?
カロリーが低いときはどうですか？
Your six categories of advice are less
あなたの6つのカテゴリーのアドバイスは少なくなります
For example, in this place, what I express with a forest-colored frame is its suggestion
たとえばこの場所で、森色のフレームで表現しているのは、その示唆です。
In fact, all stocks here are our staple food.
実際、ここにあるすべての株は私たちの主食です。
That is to say, it is suggested that three bowls of rice may be enough
つまり、ご飯は茶わん3杯で十分だということです。
But we noticed that these debilitated people eat a lot
しかし、私たちは、この衰弱した人々がたくさん食べることに気づきました。
He only needs three bowls
彼にはボウルが 3 つしか必要ない
But he ate three and a half bowls a day
しかし、彼は一日に3杯半食べました
He ate more than
彼は以上のものを食べました
Then look at this, on the other hand, this normal person eats slightly less than what he should eat
では、これを見てください。一方、この普通の人は、本来食べるべき量よりわずかに少ない量しか食べていません。
his less
彼の少ない
But as you can see, this bean fish meat egg is the so-called protein
しかし、ご覧のとおり、この豆魚肉卵はいわゆるプロテインです
All kinds of meat, eggs, seafood
あらゆる種類の肉、卵、魚介類
The weak man also eats less
弱い人は食べる量も減る
he also eats less
彼は食べる量も減ります
Normally, with this early stage of weakness, he simply exceeds the amount
通常、この初期段階の弱さでは、彼は単純に量を超えます
But are they too much protein?
しかし、タンパク質が多すぎるのでしょうか？
Actually they don't have much protein
実はタンパク質があまり多くない
Another important source is milk
もう一つの重要な供給源は牛乳です
Then our people don't drink milk
そうすれば我が国の人々は牛乳を飲まなくなります
So there's a lot of protein missing here.
つまり、タンパク質が大量に不足しているのです。
and calcium
とカルシウム
so we can see
それで私たちは見ることができます
if you're the one who didn't fall
あなたが落ちなかった人なら
Actually your protein is just right
実はあなたのプロテインはちょうどいいのです
The amount you eat is to mix milk and this
食べる量は牛乳とこれを混ぜて
Salmon are just right together
サーモンがちょうどよく合う
Of course because its protein comes from non-dairy products
もちろんタンパク質は非乳製品由来なので
Of course these people are
もちろんこの人たちは
Almost all Taiwanese are calcium deficient
台湾人はほぼ全員がカルシウム欠乏症
So our bones are a big problem
つまり私たちの骨は大きな問題なのです
For this male of these people
この人たちの中のこの男性にとって
Then the fruit didn't meet the standard
するとその果物は基準を満たさなかった
And there is not enough fat
そして脂肪が足りない
because we young people
なぜなら私たち若者は
It's all too much oil
どれも油多すぎるよ
But these old people have not reached the level of fat
しかし、これらの老人は脂肪のレベルに達していません
This grease Taiwan's grease
このグリスは台湾のグリスです
The recommended amount is the so-called five servings
推奨量はいわゆる5回分です
This is six servings
これで6人前です
is very little is six teaspoons
とても少ないです 小さじ6杯です
very little
とても少ない
But the reason none of them reach is because
でも、どれも届かない理由は、
Old people dare not eat too much oil
老人は油をあまり食べないほうがいい
So it doesn't have enough calories
そうするとカロリーが足りない
so you can see
それでわかります
a diet is
ダイエットは
slightly too much rice
ご飯が少し多すぎる
Not enough protein, not enough milk
たんぱく質が足りない、牛乳が足りない
For men, it seems that vegetables and fruits are not enough
男性には野菜や果物が足りないようです
low fat
低脂肪
So it's a situation where all kinds of things are not enough
なので色々なものが足りない状況です
Well, women have a similar trend
まあ、女性にも同様の傾向があります
The female we see is that her heat is not that big of a difference
私たちが見ている女性は、彼女の熱にそれほど大きな違いはありません
It's weak, and it didn't say anything special
弱いし、特に何も言わなかった
She basically eats much less than men
彼女は基本的に男性よりも食べる量が少ない
But no, there's not much difference between the three
でも、いいえ、この 3 つに大きな違いはありません
But this frail female is also what she almost should be.
しかし、このか弱い女性は、本来あるべき姿でもあります。
Eat an 80% full meal, three bowls, that is, almost 2:4 bowls are enough
食事を80％満腹にして3杯、つまりほぼ2:4杯で十分です。
But she ate nearly three bowls of rice
しかし、彼女はご飯を3杯近く食べました
She also has less protein
タンパク質も少ない
I don't drink this milk
この牛乳は飲みません
Very little fruit and very little fat
果物はほとんどなく、脂肪もほとんどありません
But we can see that women eat more vegetables
しかし、女性はより多くの野菜を食べていることがわかります
So it feels like protein is really a key
タンパク質が本当に重要な気がします
So we see such a diet pattern
このような食事パターンが見られます
there is an understanding
理解はある
So one of the properties just mentioned
したがって、先ほど述べたプロパティの 1 つは
That is to say, it seems that it is the time when the French people start to grow old
つまり、フランス人が老化し始める時期だそうです。
Dont still use the concept of serving food with vegetables
野菜と一緒に料理を提供するという概念をまだ使用しないでください
Because especially Taiwanese food
特に台湾料理なので
It's still rice
やはりご飯です
Nutrients in it
その中に含まれる栄養素
are not so rich
そんなに裕福ではない
protein doesn't seem to be enough
プロテインが足りないようです
There is also too little fat
脂肪も少ないし
too few calories
カロリーが少なすぎる
We know these characteristics
私たちはこれらの特徴を知っています
Then we use another angle
次に、別の角度を使用します
to explore the so-called dietary pattern
いわゆる食事パターンを調査する
Just to see how rough these six categories are.
これら 6 つのカテゴリがどの程度大まかであるかを確認するためです。
What kind of food is that person choosing?
あの人はどんな料理を選んでいる？
He's not weak
彼は弱くない
So we're going to look at this issue
そこでこの問題を見ていきます
Of course, first of all, look at the international
もちろん、まずは国際情勢に目を向けてください。
what kind of information
どのような情報ですか
Everyone knows the famous Mediterranean diet, right?
誰もが有名な地中海ダイエットを知っていますよね？
because he is so famous
彼はとても有名なので
so almost what disease
それで、ほとんど何の病気ですか
Everyone take this Mediterranean diet
皆さんもこの地中海式ダイエットを取り入れてください
let's discuss
話し合いましょう
So even debility
だから衰弱さえも
These ten are now internationally
これら 10 つは現在国際的に利用されています
The most important thing to discuss about dietary patterns is
食事パターンを議論する際に最も重要なことは、
Mediterranean Diet Discoveries
地中海食の発見
You eat more when you are middle-aged or when you are old
中年や高齢になると食べる量が増える
Long-term intake if it is in the form of Mediterranean diet
地中海食の場合は長期摂取
Less prone to frailty
虚弱になりにくい
And vice versa, if it's a Western diet
西洋的な食事の場合はその逆です。
Just a lot of red meat burgers vegetarian
赤身肉のハンバーガーだけベジタリアン
It is easier to suffer from debilitation
衰弱しやすくなる
This is a study of Westerners
これは西洋人の研究です
But after all, there is no way we can combine the Mediterranean diet
しかし結局のところ、地中海食を組み合わせることはできません
Just apply it to Taiwan
それを台湾に当てはめてみると
I can learn a little
少しは勉強できるよ
But there is no way to be completely like this
でも完全にこうなるわけがない
There is very little research on that Chinese in frailty
中国人の虚弱体質に関する研究はほとんどない
In the past there was only one Hong Kong study
過去には香港での研究は 1 件だけでした
When we published the 207 paper
207論文を発表したとき
Only Hong Kong has one
香港だけが持っています
But his entire study failed to find a relevant dietary pattern
しかし、彼の研究全体では、関連する食事パターンを見つけることができませんでした
That also has something to do with his analysis method.
それは彼の分析方法にも関係があります。
So we use what we just said
したがって、今言ったことを使用します
The data of Taiwan's nutrition and health survey
台湾の栄養と健康調査のデータ
explore this our this
これを調べてください
this debilitating diet
この衰弱的な食生活
We publish in American Geriatrics Society
米国老年医学会に掲載
Magazine, take a look
雑誌、見てください
Then what method do we use?
では、どのような方法を使うのでしょうか？
We use a simple dimensional analysis called data mining
データマイニングと呼ばれる単純な次元分析を使用します
The so-called simple-dimensional analysis method is
いわゆる単純次元解析手法は、
Think about it, don't we eat a lot of food?
考えてみてください、私たちは食べ物をたくさん食べませんか？
you have dozens of kinds you have vegetables
何十種類もあるよ 野菜もあるよ
Various fruits and vegetables with drinks
野菜や果物各種、ドリンク付き
With milk, with beans, with seafood
ミルク入り、豆入り、シーフード入り
After lots and lots of food we all went to ask
たくさん食べた後、みんなで聞きに行きました
this dimension is too big
この次元は大きすぎます
And people don't say how to eat
そして人々はどうやって食べるかについては言いません
It doesn't mean how long you eat this thing
これをどれだけ食べているかは重要ではありません
Rather it is the emergence of a form
むしろそれは形の出現です
For example, if I assume I eat a lot of red meat
たとえば、私が赤身の肉をたくさん食べると仮定すると、
I don't have room in my stomach for that
お腹にそんな余裕はないよ
For example, tofu or fish and shrimp
たとえば、豆腐や魚やエビなど
Then I may be a person who likes meat very much
そうすると、私はとても肉が好きな人になるかもしれません
I'm sure I can't eat too many vegetables
確かに野菜はあまり食べられない
Because there's no more space in my stomach
お腹にスペースがなくなったから
So food is a way of appearance
つまり、食べ物は見た目の手段です
We made such an induction
私たちはそのような誘導をしました
Then found a diet pattern
そして見つけたダイエットパターン
What about this diet?
このダイエットはどうでしょうか？
wait a minute it's in english
ちょっと待ってください、英語です
I'll use the next one to put it together
次はこれを使って組み立てていきます
This diet pattern shows that
この食事パターンが示すのは、
if you have a form
フォームをお持ちの場合
that form is
その形は
Why can't you take them apart and put them together?
なぜ分解して組み立てることができないのですか？
is what you eat
あなたが食べるものです
a lot of fruit
多くの果物
Eat more lotus seeds
蓮の実をもっと食べましょう
I also like to drink more tea
私もお茶をもっと飲みたいです
eat more vegetables
野菜ももっと食べてね
The rice you eat is also whole grains
食べるお米も全粒粉です
Then you have more protein
そうすればタンパク質がもっと摂れます
Excuses
言い訳
you drink more milk
あなたはもっと牛乳を飲みます
You also eat more fish
魚ももっと食べます
of course
もちろん
we may have a hard time saying
私たちは言いにくいかもしれない
which one is it
どちらですか
But it could also mean
しかしそれはまた意味するかもしれません
Each of these has half an eye and a little character
それぞれに半分の目と小さな特徴があります
So in summary
要約すると
The green part means
緑色の部分の意味は、
if you can
できれば
eat more than enough
十分すぎるほど食べる
plant food
植物性食品
You see this food contains vegetables
この食べ物には野菜が含まれていることがわかります
What about fruits and plants?
果物や植物はどうでしょうか？
staple food is plant-based
主食は植物性のものである
yes
はい
Nutmeg Seed Oil
荷果種子油類
The lotus seed is that it is oily
蓮の実は油っぽいのです
A sort of
一種
We divide the oil into cooking oil
油を食用油に分ける
and lotus seeds that you can eat as a snack
おやつとして食べられるハスの種
it's all oil
それはすべて油です
But it must be the lotus seed in the oil
でもそれは油の中の蓮の種に違いない
such food and drink
そんな食べ物や飲み物
So tea is a drink
つまりお茶は飲み物です
That will provide phytochemicals
それは植物化学物質を提供します
so apart from what we know
私たちが知っていることとは別に
fiber nutrients minerals
食物繊維、栄養素、ミネラル
There is also a so-called phytochemical
いわゆるフィトケミカルもあります
it will be provided
それは提供されます
So what kind of protein is it with?
では、どのようなプロテインが配合されているのでしょうか？
You can see these proteins
これらのタンパク質を見ることができます
is less saturated fat
飽和脂肪が少ない
We all know that saturated fat causes inflammation
飽和脂肪が炎症を引き起こすことは誰もが知っています
when the body is aging
体が老化すると
I just talked about the body having a low-grade inflammation
体に軽度の炎症があることについてお話しました
then this will affect
そうすればこれは影響します
Your body's protein synthesis
体のタンパク質合成
this low
この低い
So it is a less protective fat
つまり、保護脂肪が少ないのです
And it seems that the cover is quite rich
そして表紙もかなり充実しているようです
Cover quality of excuse class
言い訳クラスのカバー品質
cap quality of milk
とミルクキャップの品質
these of fish
魚のこれら
The cap quality is relatively rich
キャップの品質は比較的豊富です
some proteins
いくつかのタンパク質
Everyone knows about the fish
魚については誰もが知っています
middle of fish especially raw sea fish
魚の真ん中、特に生の海の​​魚
its omega
そのオメガ
3 omega 3 fish oil is also anti-inflammatory
3オメガ3フィッシュオイルには抗炎症作用もあります
So this combination is actually very, very reasonable.
したがって、この組み合わせは実際には非常に合理的です。
a combination of
的一個組合
OK, so according to the information just now
さて、今の情報によると
Let's sort it out and look at it like this
整理してこうやって見てみましょう
It is for the prevention and treatment of senile Mohr disease
老人性モール病の予防と治療のためです
Tips for this diet
このダイエットのヒント
The first we found was
私たちが最初に見つけたのは、
Moech disease is a variety of nutrients
モエック病はさまざまな栄養素
The condition of low intake
摂取量が少ない状態
but other than protein
でもプロテイン以外にも
These other ones we don't really know who is a key factor
これらの他のものは誰が重要な要素であるかはわかりません
Why do proteins know
なぜタンパク質は知っているのか
Because of years of research and interventions
長年にわたる研究と介入のおかげで
It means you are weak and I will give you protein
それはあなたが衰弱していることを意味します、そして私はあなたにプロテインを与えます
You see if there is such a study
そのような研究があるかどうかを見てみましょう
There is a lot of research on the headlines of this course protein
このコースの見出しにはタンパク質に関する多くの研究があります
not so sure
よくわからない
But this direction is relatively certain
しかし、この方向性は比較的確実です
So the only way is to do an intervention study
したがって、唯一の方法は介入研究を行うことです
That is to say, what you observe is sexual
つまり、あなたが観察するものは性的なものです
you put this
あなたはこれを置きました
Such a thing is given to the feeble
そんなものは弱い者に与えられる
Let's see if he eats well
彼がよく食べるかどうか見てみましょう
that's the only thing that can be proven
それが証明できる唯一のことだ
So, from the information on the diet form just now,
そこで、先ほどのダイエットフォームの情報から、
We're just thinking if
私たちが考えているのは、
We follow this in the daily dietary guidelines
私たちはこれを毎日の食事ガイドラインに従っています
This way of taking a balanced diet is recommended for the elderly
高齢者にはバランスの良い食事がおすすめ
What if he does this?
彼がこれをしたらどうなるでしょうか？
he just made sure
彼はただ確認しただけだ
Nutrients up to standard
基準を満たす栄養素
Contains protein will hit the mark
プロテインが含まれているので的中します
Of course the low calorie one
もちろん低カロリーのもの
We're going to tweak the protein
プロテインを調整してみます
Then his overall nutritional status improved
その後、全体的な栄養状態が改善しました
that might be beneficial
それは有益かもしれない
whole body system
全身系
Maintenance of function and muscle mass
機能と筋肉量の維持
That's a hypothesis we made
それは私たちが立てた仮説です
Of course it means just this
もちろんこれだけの意味です
The premise of our hypothesis is that
私たちの仮説の前提は、
there is an important
重要なことがあります
Requirements are more than 1500 calories
必要カロリーは1500カロリー以上
Protein is really okay
プロテインは本当に大丈夫
But what if it's under 1500 calories?
しかし、1500カロリー未満の場合はどうなるでしょうか？
still need to make some adjustments
まだ調整が必要です
I'm going to make some adjustments
いくつか調整を加えていきます
so we are
だから私たちは
Published in 2018
2018年発行
Proof-of-principle interventional studies
原理実証介入研究
Just put the principle
原則だけ載せておきます
put it in for a discussion
議論の対象に入れてください
designed an experiment
実験を計画した
I will first talk about the results of this experiment
まずはこの実験の結果についてお話します
Then I will say that this experiment is
それでは、この実験は次のようになります。
tell the old man how to eat
おじいさんに食べ方を教えてください
So you can refer to
したがって、参照できます
talk about it first
まずそれについて話してください
It is at the Miaoli Hospital of the Ministry of Health and Welfare
保健福祉部苗栗病院にあります
we ask them to refer some
いくつか参考にしてもらいます
After a little certification, the old man gave us an interventional study
少しの証明の後、老人は私たちに介入研究をしてくれました
Then this study is a small study
それでは、この研究は小さな研究です
Later we expanded it
後でそれを拡張しました
that in this study
この研究ではそれが
Then we divided the elderly into the control group
次に、高齢者を対照群に分けました。
do nothing
何もしない
give him some vitamin mineral powder
彼にビタミンミネラルパウダーを与えてください
And give him vitamin mineral powder
そしてビタミンミネラルパウダーを与えてください
and protein powder
そしてプロテインパウダー
There is dietary intervention
食事介入もある
It was found that other
他にもあることが分かりました
like protein powder
プロテインパウダーのような
He's also helpful.
彼も役に立ちます
a little help
少しの援助
But the real best is the food
しかし、本当に最高なのは食べ物です
an intervention
一個介入
I dropped his score from 1.4 to
私は彼のスコアを 1.4 から に下げました
0.77 means that
0.77 ということは、
Almost down 0.50 0.6
ほぼ減少 0.50 0.6
he means to say
彼は言い​​たいのです
In fact, these old people are not too serious.
実際のところ、この老人たちはそれほど深刻ではありません。
he just has 1 or 2
彼は1つか2つしか持っていない
Such an old man with thick asthenia
こんな太い無力症の老人
We can say that 50% of them are elderly
そのうちの50％が高齢者だと言えます
He lost one symptom
彼は病気で負けてしまった
Because his score dropped around 0.6
スコアが0.6くらい下がったので
probably so
おそらくそうだろう
He is remarkable for having such an effect
彼はそのような効果をもたらしたことで注目に値する
In addition, we also measured the depression of old age.
さらに、老年期のうつ病についても測定しました。
This is also found
これも見つかった
He will have a better mood
彼の機嫌は良くなるでしょう
see this phenomenon
この現象を見てください
This is what we used in a small study
これは私たちが小規模な研究で使用したものです
publish it first
まずそれを公開する
Then we did it again
それからまたやりました
This is also the sustainable plan of Academia Sinica
これは中央研究院の持続可能な計画でもあります
We conduct a large study
私たちは大規模な調査を実施します
just a little more crowded
もう少し混んでる
There are about 300 people
300人くらいいるよ
4% main
4%主
At this time, it is also paired with exercise
このとき、運動も併用します
It is the master of contrast and the master of movement
それはコントラストの達人であり、動きの達人です
Nutrition master and nutritionist exercise master
栄養マスターと栄養士運動マスター
Our intervention is
私たちの介入は、
Take a Nutritional Counseling
栄養カウンセリングを受ける
Coordination and physical fitness consultation
コーディネーションと体力の相談
Then let the old man go home and do it himself
それなら老人を家に帰って自分でやらせてください
how to make him like this
彼をこのようにするにはどうすればよいですか
as far as we found
私たちが見つけた限りでは
That's the control group is blue
それはコントロールグループが青です
Then sports nutrition in different colors
次に、さまざまな色のスポーツ栄養
Can see the drop in this sour score
この酸っぱいスコアの低下がわかります
There is a downward trend
減少傾向があります
And the nutrition group is slightly better than the exercise group
そして、栄養グループは運動グループよりわずかに優れています
Nutrition plus exercise group is best
栄養と運動のグループが最適
such a phenomenon
そのような現象
The article here is currently being revised
こちらの記事は現在修正中です
Submitted papers should be accepted
提出された論文は受理される必要があります
that's a very cheap step in
それは非常に安価なステップです
That is to say, it will not cost the country too much money to intervene
つまり、国が介入してもそれほど多額の費用がかからないということだ。
I have seen such an effect
そんな効果が見られました
What about this?
これはどうですか？
I'm coming to tell you
あなたに伝えに来ました
But how much did we change
しかし、私たちはどれだけ変わったでしょうか
In fact, very small changes are not very big
実際には、非常に小さな変化はそれほど大きくありません
So maybe I'll stop here a little bit now
じゃあ、ちょっとここでやめておこうかな
Most people might think that
ほとんどの人はこう思うかもしれない
I have vegetables and I have fruits
野菜もあるし果物もある
You asked me to eat the whole stock, and I also ate it.
出汁を全部食べてくださいと言われ、私も食べました。
You said I would eat with wheat
小麦と一緒に食べるって言ったよね
Then why is my health not as good as yours
では、なぜ私の健康状態はあなたのほど良くないのでしょうか
for example
例えば
like my words me personally
私の言葉のように、私個人としては
should be inside our lock
私たちの鍵の中にあるはずです
I'm pretty healthy
私はかなり健康です
But the bento I make with everyone every day
でも毎日みんなで作るお弁当は
that difference
その違い
That small difference means
その小さな違いが意味するのは、
Now this bento
さてこのお弁当
I looked over and said
私は振り返って言いました
too few vegetables
野菜が少なすぎる
There is enough protein, why is the rice white rice?
たんぱく質は十分にあるのに、なぜご飯は白米なのでしょうか？
That's what I've got in mind
それが私がそれを理解した方法です
So I'm going to correct it
それでは修正していきます
i go home at night
夜には家に帰ります
I just eat back the vegetables I don't have enough
足りない野菜だけ食べます
The fruit I didn't have enough also came back
足りなかった果物も戻ってきました
Then he gave me rice
それから彼は私にご飯をくれました
I might just take a little of that for myself
それを少しだけ自分用に取ってもいいかもしれない
Sprinkle that wheat germ tooth powder on it
その小麦胚芽歯磨き粉を振りかける
I'll just make a small change
ちょっとした変更を加えるだけです
Your body is different from others
あなたの体は他の人とは違います
so look over here
だからここを見てください
Control group Exercise group Nutrition group
コントロールグループ 運動グループ 栄養グループ
These four groups look at the first point
これら 4 つのグループは最初の点に注目します
Whole stock and shoulder amine is rice
まるごとだしと肩アミンはお米です
Everyone still has three months of hard work
3ヶ月もみんな頑張ってね
Nothing has changed, everyone eats the same
何も変わらない、みんな同じものを食べる
but the previous one
でも前のは
This is the control group and the exercise group
これは対照グループと演習グループです
Its protein hasn't changed either.
タンパク質も変わっていません。
but look
でも、見てください
It's the nutrition group, it's called the nutrition exercise group.
それは栄養グループであり、栄養運動グループと呼ばれます。
its increased protein
その増加したタンパク質
increased by half
半分に増えた
Half portion seems to be rare, right?
ハーフというのは珍しいのではないでしょうか？
But it adds half after all
でも結局半分も増えるんだよ
Then its milk increased by 60cc
するとミルクが60cc増えました
So these two things
したがって、これら 2 つのこと
Turns out you know we test these guys
私たちがこれらの人たちをテストしていることを知っていることがわかりました
the egg in it
その中の卵
Because there is nitrogen in the protein
タンパク質には窒素が含まれているので、
The urine egg in it is a significant increase
その中の尿卵は大幅に増加しています
For acid shock
酸性ショック用
Urinary egg means more protein is more important
尿中の卵はより多くのタンパク質がより重要であることを意味します
just add a little bit
少しだけ追加してください
it's ok
それでおしまい
Everyone eats fruits and vegetables
みんな果物や野菜を食べます
also slightly increased
もわずかに増加しました
Nutrients
果物は栄養のグループです
Probably added 0.3 servings of fruit
おそらく0.3サービングのフルーツを追加しました
But there is another interesting thing
しかし、もう一つ興味深いことがあります
because we gave them lotus
蓮をあげたから
so they added a portion and a half a day
そこで彼らは1日半を追加しました
That is, the fruit of the hour and a half
つまり、1時間半の成果
These are the old people who eat an extra tablespoon a year
これらは年に大さじ1杯余分に食べる老人たちです
all kinds of lotus
あらゆる種類の蓮
like some almonds and so on mixed together
アーモンドなどを混ぜたもののように
Also because of their increased protein
また、たんぱく質が増えるため、
It will also increase the oil of the half food
半分の食べ物の油も増えます
It may be necessary for spray toughness
スプレーの靭性のために必要な場合があります
So you think about this for a while
それで、あなたはしばらくこれについて考えます
Calories in wagashi
和菓子のカロリー
Just push it up a little bit
少しだけ押し上げてください
protein also pushed up
プロテインも押し上げられた
just such a small change
ほんの小さな変化
Let these old people burn their meat
この老人たちに肉を焼いてもらいましょう
get a big one
大きなものを手に入れる
So what I want to tell you now is
だから今私が伝えたいのは、
a little fine-tuning
少しの微調整
so you and the guy next door
だからあなたと隣の男
You see you eat almost everything
ほとんどすべてを食べていることがわかります
Why is one in shape and the other in poor health?
なぜ一方は健康で、もう一方は健康状態が悪いのでしょうか?
The bad thing is this
悪いのはこれです
But this thing for the general public
でも、これは一般人にとっては
If it wasn't for everyone coming here today
もし今日みんながここに来ていなかったら
to the general public
一般の人々へ
I want to talk to him face to face
彼と面と向かって話したい
He doesn't even want to listen
彼は聞く気すらない
you know what i mean
私の言っていることが分かるよね
so you take care of yourself now
だから今は自分のことを大事にしてください
it's not easy for you
あなたにとってそれは簡単ではありません
So I'm going to tell you about a software
そこで、あるソフトウェアについて説明します
You can go in and carefully consider what you eat.
中に入って何を食べるかを注意深く検討することができます。
worse than that standard
その基準より悪い
It's a little bit worse, you can change it
ちょっと悪いけど変えてもいいよ
it will be of great help
とても役に立つでしょう
ok this is over here
はい、ここです
This paper only mentions that
この論文ではそれについてのみ言及しています
If you are someone with different calories
カロリーが違う人なら
Together
一緒
1300 14000 15000 1600 to this
1300 14000 15000 1600 ここまで
You see, the amount of meals everyone eats is slightly different every day
ほら、みんな毎日食べる食事の量が少しずつ違うんだよ
Your protein will go up slowly
プロテインはゆっくりと増えていきます
vegetables fruit and
野菜や果物など
our word in taiwan
台湾での私たちの言葉
Our suggested dairy class is stable
私たちが提案する乳製品クラスは安定しています
no increase
増加なし
But on protein and protein
しかし、プロテインとプロテインについては
There is a scaling like this
こんな感じのスケールがあります
Then like this grease also goes up
するとこんな感じでグリスも上がります
So this data is hard to remember.
したがって、このデータは覚えておくのが困難です。
So you have to put your own data in
したがって、独自のデータを入力する必要があります
then find your combination
それからあなたの組み合わせを見つけてください
you just write it down
それを書き留めるだけです
keep for reference
参考のために保管してください
like this
このような
to do this
これをする
then we are at the place of intervention
そうすれば私たちは介入の場所にいます
how do we do it
どうやってやりますか
Then this step means that everyone can do it too.
そうすると、このステップは誰でもできるということになります。
A practice that you can follow
続けられる習慣
That is, after you see us coming in alone
つまり、私たちが一人で入ってくるのを見た後
let's see first
まずは見てみましょう
How tall and how heavy is he?
彼の身長はどれくらいですか、体重はどれくらいですか
is he male or female how old is he
彼は男性ですか、それとも女性ですか、彼は何歳ですか
we'll know
私たちは知っています
How many calories should this person eat
この人はどれくらいのカロリーを食べるべきですか
I know how many calories he eats when
彼がいつどのくらいのカロリーを食べるか知っています
I know how much he should eat
彼がどれくらい食べるべきか知っています
How much meat and how much vegetables
肉と野菜の量
Just know how much oil and how much fruit
油の量と果物の量を知ってください
We have such a data
こんなデータがあります
then this time
それから今度は
we'll ask this guy
この人に聞いてみます
that is, how do you usually eat
普段はそうやって食べてます
he described
彼は説明した
After the description, we immediately recorded it on the computer.
説明後、すぐにパソコンに記録しました
If you type a software, it will show his appearance.
ソフトウェアを入力すると彼の姿が表示されます。
the appearance of what he eats
彼が食べたものの外観
If it's not enough, ask him to make it up
それが十分でない場合は、彼に補ってもらうように頼みます
After that we'll give him a personal prescription
その後、個人的な処方箋をお渡しします
This personal prescription is very important
この個人的な処方箋は非常に重要です
It just feels like a watch
まさに時計って感じです
But everyone knows that eating is an art.
しかし、食べることが芸術であることは誰もが知っています。
That is to say, you eat like this
つまりこうやって食べるのです
he eats like that
彼はそうやって食べる
I can't always tell you
いつもは言えないけど
how many servings how many servings
何人前 何人前
Then you won't do it when you go back
じゃあ戻ったらやらないよ
So when we intervene
だから私たちが介入するときは
we have personal
私たちには個人的なものがあります
discuss with him
彼と話し合う
Just to see where he can change the most easily
彼がどこを最も簡単に変えることができるかを確認するためです
Just changed him like this
彼をこのように変えただけです
is such a way
そのような方法です
In fact, it is not easy to do interventional research.
実際、介入研究を行うのは簡単ではありません。
He just knows he probably doesn't want to do it
彼はおそらくそれをやりたくないことを知っています
so intervening
とても介入している
We also need to start talking to him about
私たちは彼と次のことについて話し始める必要もあります
Hey, do you know you have debilitating disease?
ねえ、あなたは衰弱性の病気を患っていることを知っていますか？
Hey, do you know what frailty is?
ねえ、フレイルって知ってる？
Then he went to the hospital to test
それから彼は検査のために病院に行きました
He couldn't walk so he went to the hospital
彼は歩くことができなかったので病院へ行きました
He would have liked the doctor to help him
彼は医者に助けてほしかっただろう
But the doctor can't help with this disease
でも医者はこの病気を助けることはできない
So the doctor referred him to us
それで医者は彼を私たちに紹介しました
then we told him
それから私たちは彼に言いました
Do you know your weakness
自分の弱さを知っていますか
is replyable
返信可能です
but you have to cooperate with us
しかし、あなたは私たちに協力しなければなりません
you only need to eat nutrition
食べればいいのは栄養だけ
you can reply
返信できます
After gaining such a trust from him
彼からこれほどの信頼を得てからは、
We'll just tell him what to do after that
その後どうするかを彼に教えるだけです
After talking about how you should eat
どうやって食べようかと話し合った後、
How to eat how to eat, then you have to ask him
どうやって食べるか、どうやって食べるか、それからあなたは彼に尋ねなければなりません
Will you have trouble doing this?
これを行うのに問題はありますか?
He told people that he had difficulties
彼は自分には困難があると人々に話した
Because I don't cook the food at home
家でご飯作らないから
Or it means that my family usually buys this kind of thing
というか、うちの家族はこういうものをよく買うということですね
Then we're going to work it out with him.
それから彼と一緒に解決してみます。
these questions
これらの質問
Then these problems are also encountered by everyone.
そして、これらの問題は誰もが遭遇するものでもあります。
You may have listened to the speech today and you go back and want to change it
今日のスピーチを聞いて、戻って内容を変更したいと思うかもしれません。
But your food is not made by you at all
でもあなたの食べ物はあなたが作ったものではまったくありません
so you have to talk to your family
だから家族と話し合う必要がある
the other half
残りの半分
your child
あなたの子供
or your family
またはあなたの家族
Who is in charge to do a consultation
相談の担当者は誰ですか
discuss
議論
of course we have
もちろん持っています
It depends on the level of understanding of Hirao's case.
この事件を理解できるかどうかはヒララにかかっている。
he has some unhappy things
彼には不幸なことがある
Let's let him vent his emotions, wait
彼に感情を解放させましょう ちょっと待ってください
A methodology for nutrition education with a few, many
少人数、多人数による栄養教育の方法論
to do
すること
Then track after the first month
その後、最初の 1 か月後に追跡されます
A methodology for repeating these nutrition education
これらの食育を繰り返すための方法論
Ping Liang then let him release his emotions
平良は感情を解放させた
Build a supportive relationship with him
彼と協力的な関係を築く
Think of alternatives with him
彼と一緒に代替案を考える
then one month to three months
それから1ヶ月から3ヶ月
We also gave him some rewards
私たちは彼にもいくつかのご褒美を与えました
Sign some consent forms with him too.
彼と一緒に同意書にも署名してください。
Say I'm willing to change like this
このように変わりたいと言ってください
There are many methodologies in this
これにはたくさんの方法論があります
Well then I'll be next
じゃあ次は私が行きます
start talking about this
このことについて話し始める
A tool we used at the time
当時使っていた道具
We used a standard dinner plate
スタンダードなディナープレートを使用しました
what about this plate
この皿はどうですか
is available
利用可能です
this plate is
このプレートは
if you are interested
もし興味があれば
You can go online to Tang Diabetes Association
Tang Diabetes Association にオンラインでアクセスできます
Maybe three or four hundred yuan.
おそらく300元か400元でしょう。
Then its easy thing to do is
それから、それを行うのは簡単です
it has three holes on this side
こちら側には穴が3つあります
if you should have one
持っているべきなら
you should eat four
4つ食べるべきです
If you have a few copies, you can fill it up.
数枚あればいっぱいにできます。
Then this place is two servings of vegetables
じゃあここは野菜2人前
so it's one meal at a time
だから一度に一食です
such a plan
そのような計画
then here
それからここで
here is
ここは
This city meeting is the location of rice
この市会議は米の場所です
fruit location
果物の場所
location of milk
ミルクの場所
oil location
油の場所
Each of our nutritionists
栄養士一人ひとりが
We designed this for him
私たちは彼のためにこれをデザインしました
This person will tell the nutritionist
この人は栄養士に伝えます
say what i eat
私が何を食べるかを言う
The nutritionist probably drew a picture
栄養士さんが絵を描いたのでしょう
i found this guy
私はこの男を見つけました
It's all protein
全部プロテインだよ
six servings of protein
プロテイン6食分
this is his night
これは彼の夜です
I will eat so many dishes at noon
お昼にはたくさんの料理を食べます
Such a dish at night
夜はこんな料理も
he has two servings of vegetables
彼は野菜を二食分持っている
His meal looks like this
彼の食事はこんな感じです
how much milk does he drink
彼はどれくらい牛乳を飲みますか
he has fried ham
彼はハムを揚げた
This ham dish is a bit oily
このハム料理は少し油っぽいです
fried vegetables with oil
野菜の油炒め
he's like that
彼はそのような人です
after evaluating it
評価してから
There is a number here
ここに数字があります
this number
この番号
This number can be compared with this person's
この数字はこの人の数字と比較できます
actually
実際
Take it and check it
手に取って確認してください
What about after matching?
マッチング後はどうでしょうか？
we might just tell it again
もう一度言ってみようかな
Your next three meals will be divided like this
次の3食はこのように分けられます
you have a glass of milk in the morning
あなたは朝コップ一杯の牛乳を飲みます
eat two slices of toast
トーストを2枚食べる
It is best to have a toast with some lotus fruit
蓮の実で乾杯するのが最高です
Whether it is placed separately or
別々に置いてもいいし、
It's fruit toast
フルーツトーストです
Two servings of Chinese food
中華料理2人前
a bit of meat and an egg
少しの肉と卵
then two servings of vegetables
それから野菜を2食分
Served with whole bone rice and a fruit
全骨ご飯とフルーツを添えて
Then you can also pair a
その後、ペアリングすることもできます
This dessert is like a yogurt for dessert
このデザートはデザート用のヨーグルトのようなものです
Then dinner is two protein courses
その後、夕食はプロテインコース2品です
A dish like this
こんな料理も
a piece of fruit a whole bone meal
果物一切れ 全骨粉
Just help it make a plan like this
このような計画を立てるのを手伝ってください
For example, a person eats a lot
たとえば、人はたくさん食べる
2100 kcal
2100kcal
it even has protein in the morning
朝はプロテインも摂れます
I ate porridge in the morning, etc.
朝お粥などを食べました。
It is also a plan like this
こんな企画もあります
so a dinner plate like this
ということでディナープレートはこんな感じ
You can also use this to help you
これを使用して支援することもできます
For example, you should eat
たとえば、食べるべきです
For example, four servings of protein
たとえば、プロテイン4食分
That's four servings, about
それは約4回分です
has an auxiliary effect
補助的な効果がある
So in our study just now
それで、今私たちの研究では
Just use the same method just now for the nutritionist to use
栄養士が使用するのと同じ方法を使用するだけです
what about this plate
この皿はどうですか
We also sent each case a copy
また、各ケースにコピーを送信しました
and we put food models on the plate
そして、お皿に食べ物の模型を置きます
This is 500 calories
これで500カロリーです
Maybe a plate with 700 kcal
一皿で700kcalくらいかな
We also gave it fruit and milk powder
フルーツや粉ミルクも与えました
Because it was done in the Miaoli area
苗栗地区でやったから
People in Miaoli do not drink milk powder very much
苗栗の人は粉ミルクをあまり飲みません
And he is not used to buying wagashi
そして彼は和菓子を買うことに慣れていない
so we want to say
だから私たちは言いたいのです
It's better to send them when we start to intervene
我々が介入し始めたら送ったほうがいいよ
Otherwise he might just listen
そうでなければ、彼はただ聞くだけかもしれません
So this is sending
それで、これは送信しています
so that he can remember
彼が思い出せるように
We also designed a restaurant
レストランのデザインもさせていただきました
Let him take this restaurant home
彼にこのレストランを家に持って帰らせてください
This is the size of a normal restaurant
これは一般的なレストランのサイズです
put him on the table
彼をテーブルの上に置きます
So he knows that 500 calories will look like this
つまり、彼は500カロリーが次のようになることを知っています
His family can also see
彼の家族も見ることができます
His plate should look like this
彼の皿は次のようになっているはずです
That 600 calories looks like this
600カロリーはこんな感じ
So you can see that the difference is very small
違いが非常に小さいことがわかります
but everyone is different
でもみんな違う
Then here are some references
それから、ここにいくつかの参考資料があります
five hundred six hundred seven hundred and eight hundred
五百六百七十八百
That's a very small drawing
とても小さな絵ですね
Make some reference for his family
彼の家族に参考にしてください
But every old man wants to
しかし、老人なら誰でもそうしたいのです
His meal might look like this
彼の食事はこんな感じかも
OK so
はい、それでは
This is how we intervene
これが私たちが介入する方法です
but i'm going to talk a little bit about this
でもこれについて少し話します
This section provides individual prescriptions
このセクションでは個別の処方箋を提供します
Because everyone eats differently
食べ方は人それぞれなので
we will encounter many problems
私たちは多くの問題に遭遇するでしょう
For example, some people
たとえば、ある人たちは、
he just doesn't drink milk
彼はただ牛乳を飲まないだけです
For example, we have to discuss with him
たとえば、私たちは彼と話し合わなければなりません
There was an old man who said
こう言った老人がいました
I drink three in one in the morning
朝はスリーインワンを飲みます
he speaks like this
彼はこのように話します
I drink three in one
3つを1つにして飲みます
then we know he likes coffee
それから彼がコーヒーが好きだとわかります
so i told him
だから私は彼に言いました
Then why don't you go and buy some coffee powder?
それならコーヒー粉を買いに行きませんか？
buy more brown sugar
もっと黒砂糖を買ってください
buy another can of milk powder
別の粉ミルクの缶を買う
you put the three together
あなたはその3つを組み合わせました
It's very similar to your three-in-one
スリーインワンとよく似ています
we'll make the suggestion
私たちが提案します
Some people say I just don't eat fruit
私が果物を食べないだけだと言う人もいます
then you have to find a way
それなら方法を見つけなければなりません
then would you like
それではよろしいでしょうか
For example, some dried fruit
例えばドライフルーツなど
These things can also be replaced
こういったものも交換可能です
raisins or something
レーズンか何か
Or really don't want to eat
もしくは本当に食べたくない
100% fruit juice though not the best
100％フルーツジュースですが、最高ではありません
is also an applied method
応用方法でもあります
it lacks protein
タンパク質が不足しています
Like, for example, I came across a case
たとえば、あるケースに遭遇したとします。
Of course, I'm not there to intervene there every day.
もちろん、私は毎日そこに介入するためにそこにいるわけではありません。
I run over every week to have a look
毎週見に行ってます
When encountering a case, it will tell me
事件に遭遇すると教えてくれる
I have three highs, what protein do I eat?
ハイが3回あるのですが、どのようなプロテインを摂取すればよいでしょうか?
Then we have to tell it with evidence
それなら証拠を持って語らなければなりません
various scientific displays
さまざまな科学的展示
Protein can not only lower blood pressure
プロテインは血圧を下げるだけではありません
Can also help control your blood sugar
血糖値のコントロールにも役立ちます
If you're eating the right kind of protein
適切な種類のタンパク質を摂取していれば
red meat
赤身肉
If there are more tofu and fish
豆腐と魚がもっとあれば
Because cholesterol doesn't rise either
コレステロールも上がらないので
talk to it
それに話してください
some people have too much protein
タンパク質が多すぎる人もいます
if too much
多すぎる場合
You have to change the form of the dish
料理の形を変えないといけない
For example, I always like big pieces of meat.
たとえば、私は大きな肉が好きでした。
Now you may have some dishes that use shredded pork
豚肉の細切りを使った料理もあるかもしれません
as delicious
美味しいほど
So these are negotiable
したがって、これらは交渉可能です
where to buy
どこで買う
And some people are health conscious
そして健康志向の人もいる
All dishes are hot
どの料理も温かいです
We also have to tell it that this is not good
これは良くないことも伝えなければなりません
you still have to use oil
まだ油を使わなければなりません
to cook because of the oil
油があるから料理する
Provides calories for the elderly and has a full vitamin coat
高齢者向けのカロリーを提供し、フルビタミンコートを備えています。
It's a good thing, why don't I use it all?
それは良いことです、なぜそれをすべて使わないのですか？
It's wrong to cook all dishes hot
すべての料理を熱く調理するのは間違いです
So these kinds of questions are different for everyone.
したがって、この種の質問は人によって異なります。
You have to break them one by one.
一つ一つ壊さなければなりません。
So dietary intervention is really not easy
したがって、食事介入は実際には簡単ではありません
if not do
そうしない場合
We saw many people on Wenyan
ウェンヤンではたくさんの人に会った
After teaching people how to eat, there is no effect at all
食べ方を教えても全く効果がない
Just because he not only needs to know the prescription
処方箋を知る必要があるだけではないからです
And also, that prescription needs to be personalized.
また、その処方箋は個人に合わせてカスタマイズする必要があります。
but also in line with his personal form
しかし、それは彼の個人的なフォームに沿ったものでもあります
So I guess this is when you guys go back
それで、これが皆さんが戻るときだと思います
a problem that everyone will face
誰もが直面するであろう問題
Then this is what we ask the elderly to fill in every day
これは私たちが高齢者に毎日記入してもらうものです
how much did he eat
彼はどれくらい食べましたか
When you fill in this every day
これを毎日記入すると
It also reminds him again and again that he must meet the standard.
また、基準を満たさなければならないことを何度も思い出させられました。
OK so we just told you about this
OK、これについては先ほどお話しました
How is he in terms of nutritional entry research?
栄養学的エントリーの研究に関してはどうですか?
That is to say, there are many literatures that provide caloric supplements
つまり、カロリーサプリメントを提供する文献は数多くあります。
or protein calorie supplement
またはプロテインカロリーサプリメント
This kind of research generally tends to be good
この種の研究は一般に良い結果が得られる傾向があります
but not exactly the same
しかし全く同じではありません
Generally speaking, if this type of
一般的にこのタイプの場合、
Recording research if paired with exercise
運動と組み合わせた場合の研究の記録
Usually there are more positive effects
通常はもっとプラスの効果があります
But from our records study we found that
しかし、私たちの記録調査から、次のことが分かりました。
If the principle of balanced diet
バランスのとれた食事の原則であれば、
Interventions that Provide Personalized Nutrition
個人に合わせた栄養を提供する介入
in the case of supplements such as it
そういったサプリメントの場合は
what we feel it is
私たちがそれを感じていること
We found that it is possible to improve
改善できることが分かりました
Overall nutritional status Post-fall status and level of depression
全体的な栄養状態 転倒後の状態とうつ病のレベル
and we have other single use nutrients
他にも使い捨ての栄養素があります
This supplement is not as effective as the food itself
このサプリメントは食品そのものほど効果的ではありません
This is one of our record research
これは私たちの記録研究の一つです
come to such a conclusion
そのような結論に達する
OK, after this point
OK、この時点から
Then there is another issue of geriatric syndrome, which is
それから、もう一つの老人症候群の問題があります。
Dementia
認知症
We started to do this
私たちはこれをやり始めました
But in this so-called observation belief
しかし、このいわゆる観察信念では
This step in data mining
データマイニングのこのステップ
Let me do some simple summary for you
簡単にまとめてみます
That is, first of all, we take a look and we find that
つまり、まず第一に、見てみると、次のことがわかります。
this so-called short intelligence test for the elderly
このいわゆる高齢者向けの簡易知能検査
There is a short test called MMSC
MMSCという短いテストがあります
It can measure all aspects of the intelligence of the elderly
高齢者の知能をあらゆる側面から測定できる
Then we have done something like this in Nutrition University
それから栄養大学ではこんなことをやりました。
We found that starting at age 65
65歳から始まることがわかりました
This intelligence will fall down
この知性は崩壊するだろう
male female or overall
男性女性または全体
we use this score
このスコアを使用します
Come do some diet research with this
これを使ってダイエット研究をしてみませんか
that's in constitution
それは憲法にある
If we look at the International Constitution, we find
国際憲法を見てみると、
There are quite a lot of nutrients that are closely related to Shi Zhi
士志と関係の深い栄養素がかなり多い
Contains Vitamin B Complex Vitamin C Vitamin E Vitamin D
ビタミンB群、ビタミンC、ビタミンE、ビタミンDが含まれています
There are also various plant chemicals
植物化学物質もいろいろあります
Then it's not the same as this debility
それなら、この衰弱とは同じではありません
Debilitating many clinical trials are doing protein
多くの臨床試験では衰弱させるためにプロテインが使用されています
But Shi Zhi's research is very little
しかし石志の研究は非常に少ない。
And it's all small
そしてそれはすべて小さいです
research, now it is found that there are several studies
研究では、いくつかの研究があることが判明しました
Such research on delaying cognitive decline
認知機能低下の遅延に関するこのような研究
Effective research finds almost all in mild cognitive impairment
効果的な研究により、ほぼ全員が軽度認知障害であることが判明
It's just that it's starting to drop a little bit
ただ、少しずつ下がり始めています
If it's serious, it's almost useless
本気ならほぼダメ
So this demented anti-intelligence is to find
それで、この精神薄弱者が探しているのは、
If it is too late, at most it will stop thinking and it won't get worse
遅すぎる場合は、せいぜい思考を停止するだけで、悪化することはありません
There is one study that is the most significant
最も重要な研究が 1 つあります
What it shows is that it can be almost with relative certainty
比較的確実であることがほぼ可能であることが判明
It is the intervention of vitamin B group
ビタミンB群の介入です
vitamin B group it has several B
ビタミンB群にはいくつかのBが含まれています
Like 8 folic acid Vitamin B2 Vitamin B6
8 葉酸 ビタミンB2 ビタミンB6 など
These are all related to the synthesis of our neurotransmitters
これらはすべて神経伝達物質の合成に関連しています。
Then this group B research is done
その後、このグループ B の研究が完了します
There is a group B study my current author's name I forgot
グループBの研究がありますが、現在の著者の名前は忘れました
They do it very carefully and they use MR
彼らは非常に慎重に作業を行っており、MRを使用しています
To measure the volume of the brain
脳の体積を測るには
It was found that the head and nose group can significantly slow down this atrophy
頭と鼻のグループはこの萎縮を大幅に遅らせることができることが判明しました
It is now the only study in the world
それは現在世界で唯一の研究です
This is what works great
これが素晴らしい効果です
But we believe that influencing this
しかし、私たちはこれに影響を与えていると信じています
There are many factors for this dementia
この認知症には多くの要因があります
just say it cuts in with nutrients
栄養素をカットすると言うだけです
is to see the nose group
鼻のグループを見ることです
there are many more
他にもたくさんあります
Now there are actually a lot of this
今は本当にこういうのがたくさんあるよ
Industry is
業界は
Industry is called industry, it should be called manufacturer
産業は産業と呼ばれ、メーカーと呼ばれるべきです
now i know
今私は知っている
Because I participated in a Shi Zhi Certification Conference in Europe last year
昨年ヨーロッパで行われた士志認定カンファレンスに参加したためです。
They are developing some silver products
彼らはいくつかのシルバー製品を開発しています
Some silver items to see if they can help Shi Zhi
Shi Zhiを助けることができるかどうかを確認するためのいくつかの銀のアイテム
There must be nose groups in that silver product.
その銀製品にはノーズグループが入っているはずです。
But with a lot of other things
しかし、他の多くのことと一緒に
so this
したがって、この
Then our laboratory is currently working on a mineral
さて、私たちの研究室では現在鉱物の研究を行っています。
Look at its relationship with this dementia
この認知症との関係を見てみましょう
OK, what about the nutritional health survey?
さて、栄養健康調査についてはどうですか？
I also found that it was with this lion
このライオンと一緒だった事も分かりました
It's the people with low MMSC scores
MMSCスコアが低い人たちです
He's basically a lot of stuff
彼は基本的にたくさんのことを持っています
very low heat
非常に低い熱
Protein fat with carbohydrates B1 B2 B
タンパク質、脂肪、炭水化物 B1 B2 B
B3 is nice B6 B1 CDE
B3はいいですね B6 B1 CDE
Fake calcium core iron
偽カルシウムコア鉄
Fatty acids regardless of saturated units
飽和単位を問わない脂肪酸
low cholesterol
低コレステロール
low fiber
低繊維
So here is a phenomenon that appears when people get old
人が年をとると現れる現象です
Usually not all heart disease in the past
通常、過去にすべての心臓病があったわけではありません
high cholesterol
高コレステロール
but by then
でもそれまでに
You have heart disease and high cholesterol
心臓病と高コレステロールを患っている
At that time, it was not high anymore. They all came down.
その時はもう水位は高くなくて、みんな降りてきました。
So this time is to eat more
ということで、今回はもっと食べてみようと思います
To eat more is a key point
もっと食べることが大切です
So this is already entering another
つまり、これはすでに別のものに入っています
a question from the era
時代からの問い
What about diet?
ダイエットについてはどうですか？
A little more research room
もう少し研究室
other than the mediterranean diet
地中海食以外にも
There is another one called Deshu Diet
デシュダイエットと呼ばれるものもあります
this is the famous
これは有名です
Our Blood Pressure Diet
私たちの血圧ダイエット
And these two combinations
そしてこの2つの組み合わせ
It is built by the Mediterranean Sea. The English name is Mediterranean.
地中海に面して建っており、英語名はMediterraneanといいます。
Teshu diet called Dash
ダッシュと呼ばれるテツリーダイエット
Just M and D
ちょうどMとD
It's the Maddie diet
それがマディダイエットです
All three have been seen
3人とも見たことある
Protective effect on cognitive function
認知機能に対する保護効果
but basically forward-looking
でも基本的には前向き
is now to measure you have a diet like this
あなたがこのような食生活をしているかどうかを測定します
You won't lose your mind easily
簡単に正気を失うことはないだろう
like this
このような
What this diet emphasizes is
このダイエットで重視しているのは、
Whole fruit and fruit seeds
丸ごとの果物と果物の種子
milk tea
ミルクティー
everyone looks like
みんな似てる
Acid meat disease is a bit like
酸性肉病はちょっと似ています
but not exactly the same
しかし全く同じではありません
There are milk eggs here, have you seen it?
ここに乳卵がありますが、見たことがありますか？
Just Acid Meat Syndrome has no dairy eggs at all
Just Acid Meat Syndromeには乳卵がまったく含まれていません
Just sour flesh is the synthesis of muscle
ただ酸っぱい肉は筋肉の合成です
are all fish
みんな魚です
Shelfish is
シェルフリッシュは
borrow class
藉可類
seafood
海鮮
something like this
このようなもの
The same is the tea
お茶も同じです
This is what the West sees
これが西洋人が見ているものです
then we Taiwan
それから私たち台湾
We also published an article
記事も掲載させていただきました
is the most 2018
2018年が一番
It seems that only recently 2018 is an electronic file
2018年になってようやく電子ファイル化されたようです
This is that Galliproof is the draft
これは Galliproof がドラフトであるということです
is the first edition of typesetting
初版です
Later, it should be a study that came out at the beginning of this year.
あとは、今年の初めに出た研究のはずです。
We are referring to the nutritional adjustment data
栄養調整データを参考にしています
It's always been said that if your score is demented
スコアが認知症だといつも言われています。
just have this dementia score
この認知症スコアを持っているだけです
how is your diet
あなたの食生活はどうですか
Let's look at what you ate twenty years ago
20年前に何を食べたか見てみましょう
relationship with subsequent dementia
その後の認知症との関係
To do this this paper brings together two studies
これを行うために、この論文では 2 つの研究をまとめています
As a result, we see that we divide men and women separately
その結果、男性と女性を別々に分けていることがわかります。
All found this rich image of diet type factor
全員がこの豊富な食事タイプ要因のイメージを発見しました
In terms of integration, of course, the sequence is a little different.
もちろん、統合に関しては、順序が少し異なります。
In general, there are many fruits
全体的にフルーツが多いですね
Lots of vegetables, lots of lotus seeds, lots of whole fruits and miscellaneous grains
たくさんの野菜、たくさんの蓮の種、たくさんの丸ごとの果物と雑穀
breakfast slices
朝食のスライス
The most important thing is that Yan sells the film
最も重要なことはヤンが映画を売ることだ
Eggs Dairy Seafood Tea & Coffee
卵 乳製品 シーフード 紅茶とコーヒー
This one looks like Shulton
これはシュルトンに似てる
Like the Maddie Diet with Shulton
シュルトンのマディ・ダイエットのように
very much like frailty but you can see
虚弱に非常に似ていますが、わかります
Egg
卵
This appearance of the egg, the appearance of the milk egg
この卵の姿、乳卵の姿
I want to say it's an interventional study with that group B.
それはそのグループBに対する介入研究だと言いたいのです。
There is a mutual echo, that is, the B group is related to the brain
相互エコーがある、つまりBグループは脳に関係している
So the protein that comes out here will have eggs
ここで出てくるタンパク質には卵が含まれます
dairy comes out very clearly
乳製品が非常にはっきりと出てくる
Then there are also tea and coffee
あとは紅茶やコーヒーもあります
That tea and coffee are the same
紅茶とコーヒーは同じだということ
Orthocarcin is very rich in Orthocarcin, which has antioxidant energy
オルトカルシンには抗酸化エネルギーを持つオルトカルシンが豊富に含まれています。
And there's some caffeine in it for a drink like this
そして、このような飲み物にはカフェインが含まれています
So after I see a result like this
このような結果を見た後
I think the diet of the last group of the elderly can be integrated
最後の高齢者グループの食生活を統合できると思います
Because frailty is not that different from dementia
フレイルは認知症とそれほど変わらないから
It is these proteins that must be taken care of
注意しなければならないのはこれらのタンパク質です
it's probably almost
おそらくほぼです
So what we just talked about in the dementia part is
認知症の部分で今話したのは、
We found that the caloric intake of elderly people with dementia is low
認知症高齢者のカロリー摂取量が低いことが判明
Significantly lower levels of many trace elements
多くの微量元素のレベルが大幅に低下
Including those things that should not be high
高くてはいけないものも含めて
like cholesterol and saturated fat
コレステロールや飽和脂肪など
Originally, we all said that it must be low and low.
もともと、低く低くないといけないとみんなで言っていました。
Now both of those things are down too
今ではそれらの両方もダウンしています
also lowered
も下げられました
On the contrary, it means your cholesterol, but dont limit it
逆にコレステロールを意味しますが、制限しないでください
Don't limit the meat
肉を制限しないでください
Because now it's just a matter of eating too little
今はただ食べる量が少ないだけだから
What about the elderly with good cognitive function?
認知機能が良好な高齢者はどうでしょうか？
We just saw fresh fruit
ちょうど新鮮な果物を見ました
Wagyu whole milk protein rich food
和牛全乳たんぱく質豊富な食品
Like men are fish and sea bream
人間は魚や鯛のようなもの
Women are eggs or soy products
女性は卵か大豆製品
and tea and coffee
そして紅茶とコーヒー
a form of sauce
ソースの一種
So what we have in Taiwan is different from the international ones.
したがって、台湾にあるものは国際的なものとは異なります。
is very consistent
非常に一貫しています
In addition, prospective studies
さらに、前向き研究
I just talked about prospective studies
先ほど前向き研究についてお話しました
we have another profile
別のプロフィールがあります
found that 20 years ago in the 1990s
20年前の1990年代に発見された
If these people happen to be
もしこの人たちがたまたまそうなったら、
If you like to eat fish and drink tea
魚を食べてお茶を飲むのが好きなら
He was in 2000 2010
彼は 2000 年と 2010 年に
less risk of dementia
認知症のリスクが少ない
So there is a long-term and a short-term
つまり、長期と短期があるのです
there is a little different news
少し違うニュースがあります
In the long run, it starts from middle age
長い目で見れば中年から始まる
Of course you want to prevent cardiovascular disease
心血管疾患を予防したいのはもちろん
This kind of thing like three high
三高みたいなこういうこと
let this risk down
このリスクを軽減しましょう
Then this I believe this plays such a role
それからこれはそういう役割を果たしていると思います
but in the short term
しかし短期的には
You need to get enough nutrients
十分な栄養素を摂取する必要があります
Group B is enough
グループBだけで十分
enough protein
十分なタンパク質
tea or enough
お茶でも十分
These two are somewhat similar but
この二つはちょっと似ていますが、
different face
違う顔
so we just
だから私たちはただ
Combining the above information?
上記の情報を組み合わせると?
We're in the National Construction Agency's program
私たちは建設庁のプログラムに参加しています
we suggest
私たちは提案します
The key to the prevention and treatment of geriatric syndrome
老人症候群の予防と治療の鍵
Diet content
食事内容
should mean
意味するはずです
The first point
最初のポイント
You must balance the six categories
6 つのカテゴリのバランスを取る必要があります
Then of course we have to deal with those who set up twelve
それからもちろん、12を設定した人たちに対処しなければなりません
The allocation of these six categories should be adjusted
これら 6 つのカテゴリの割り当てを調整する必要があります
We must emphasize what I just said
私が今言ったことを強調しなければなりません
Vegetables, Nuts, Seeds, Mushrooms, Milk
野菜、ナッツ、種子、きのこ、牛乳
and protein-rich foods
そしてたんぱく質が豊富な食べ物
with healthy tea
健康茶と一緒に
In terms of protein, what is better for the elderly?
タンパク質に関しては、高齢者にとって何が良いのでしょうか？
Fish and seafood include excuses
魚介類には言い訳が含まれます
What about eggs, beans, meat?
卵、豆、肉はどうでしょうか？
Less red meat but I must say
赤身肉は少ないですが、言わなければなりません
We didn't see red meat in our film and television mentality just now
私たちは今、映画やテレビの考え方に赤身の肉を見ていませんでした
but it means to say
しかしそれは言うことを意味します
People who eat less red meat
赤身の肉をあまり食べない人
Other people who eat a lot of meat are good
肉をたくさん食べる他の人は良いです
But let's analyze these carefully
しかし、これらを注意深く分析しましょう
People with fewer lions and less lean meat
ライオンの数が少なく、赤身の肉が少ない人々
Does he eat red meat? He still does.
彼は赤身の肉を食べますか? 今でも食べています。
So I want to emphasize again
そこで、もう一度強調したいのですが、
I'm not telling you to go back
戻れとは言ってないよ
Just eat white meat
白い肉だけ食べてね
And then there's just these things, no pork at all
そして、これらのものだけがあり、豚肉はまったくありません
i definitely didn't mean that
決してそんなつもりではなかった
Because our Taiwanese society
なぜなら私たちの台湾社会は
Pork is a major protein
豚肉は主要なたんぱく質です
Its whole suggested implication is that
その示唆される全体的な意味は次のとおりです
Pork and other proteins should be evenly distributed
豚肉とその他のタンパク質は均等に分散される必要があります
Not much pork, absolutely not much
豚肉はあまり多くありません、絶対に多くありません
but not at all
しかし、まったくそうではありません
The reason I remind everyone is because
私が皆さんに思い出させる理由は、
in taiwanese
台湾語で
Pork is a major source of vitamin B1
豚肉はビタミンB1の主要な供給源です
Can't say not to rule it all out
全てを排除しないとは言えない
don't go don't do anything
行かないで何もしないでください
don't go too far
あまり遠くに行かないでください
we're talking about a trend
私たちはトレンドについて話しています
so understand
だからわかります
OK, so our intervention goal
OK、介入目標を設定します
We are doing the same in the community now
私たちは今コミュニティでも同じことをしています
The first time we met an old man
初めて老人に会ったとき
We're going to estimate his personal calories
彼の個人的なカロリーを推定してみます
Then we understand his six categories of allocation
次に、彼の 6 つの割り当てカテゴリーを理解します。
we are going to tell him
私たちは彼に言うつもりです
and then assign it
そしてそれを割り当てます
How to adjust the distribution of the four major food categories of his main meal
主食の 4 つの主要な食品カテゴリーの配分を調整する方法
what kind of staple food
主食は何ですか
what kind of entree
どのような前菜ですか
what kind of vegetables
どのような野菜ですか
what kind of fruit to match
どんなフルーツが合うのか
What about the allocation?
配分はどうなるのでしょうか？
we would recommend using some
いくつか使用することをお勧めします
This kind of dinner plate in three-dimensional space
立体空間ではこんなディナープレート
you can easily understand
簡単に理解できます
Then we ordinary people
それでは私たち一般人は
you can buy one
1つ購入できます
after understanding
理解した上で
Been yours for a while
しばらくの間あなたのものでした
Quantity is in your head
量は頭の中にある
Where do you go out in the future, let alone take it with you
将来どこに出かけるの、ましてや持って行きますか？
probably will know
おそらく知っているでしょう
That's another way to creatively
それもクリエイティブな方法です
There are some things you may not normally be used to
普段は慣れないこともありますが、
You have to have some imagination and creativity since childhood
子供の頃から想像力と創造力が必要です
mix it in
混ぜてください
this event we
このイベント私たちは
Many friends are playing all day long
たくさんの友達が一日中遊んでいます
how to play this match how to match
この試合のプレイ方法 試合方法
Then post it on Facebook.
次に、それを Facebook に投稿します。
Then pass it back and forth in LINE
あとはLINEでやりとりする
Very interesting
とても興味深い
This can be turned into an event
これはイベント化できる
So at the caring base
だからケアベースで
we tell old people
私たちは老人たちに言います
Just say you must press your own heat
自分の熱を押し出す必要があるとだけ言ってください
eat enough
十分に食べる
You have to balance the six high-quality categories
6つの高品質カテゴリーのバランスをとる必要があります
what does this mean
これは何を意味するのでしょうか
That is, every type of food must be eaten
つまり、あらゆる種類の食べ物を食べなければなりません
but no more no less
でもそれ以上でもそれ以下でもない
Of course, the type of food is to be diversified.
もちろん、食べ物の種類も多様化するはずです。
Strive for change
変化を求めて努力する
Then each category must choose high density
次に、各カテゴリは高密度を選択する必要があります
Let's talk a little bit about the high density
高密度について少し話しましょう
For example, white rice is low density
例えば白米は密度が低い
All shares are high density
すべてのシェアは高密度です
It is nutrient dense
栄養豊富です
Everyone understands this, it is high density and low density.
誰でもわかる、高密度と低密度
Over processed is low density, under processed is high density
処理が過剰な場合は密度が低く、処理が不十分な場合は密度が高くなります
So if you really want to eat healthy, sometimes you have to do it yourself
ですから、本当に健康的な食事をしたいのであれば、時には自分でやらなければなりません
Like me, although I am so busy, I am doing research at Academia Sinica
私も同じように、とても忙しいですが、中央研究院で研究をしています。
I cook it myself for my family every breakfast and every dinner
家族のために朝食と夕食ごとに自分で作ります
Ready to leave the office at 5:30 and rush home to cook dinner for the whole family
5:30にオフィスを出て、急いで家に帰って家族全員の夕食を作る準備をします
Because I want to make sure I eat healthy and my family eats healthy
自分も家族も健康的な食事を心がけたいから
So it's good to do it a little bit
だからちょっとやってみると良いよ
good condition for a busy job
忙しい仕事に適した状態
A glass of plant drink a day
1日1杯の植物ドリンク
So this is to say that eating enough calories means eating enough
つまり、十分なカロリーを食べるということは、十分な量を食べるということです
Eat enough calories, eat enough, high-quality big food is good to eat
十分なカロリーを食べて、十分に食べて、高品質で大きな食べ物を食べるのは良いことです
Last but not least because you might not be able to eat it
最後になりますが、食べられなくなる可能性があるので
or when it's time to eat, so the events we do in the community
または食事の時間になったとき、コミュニティで行うイベント
It is to teach the old man to know his dinner plate, to teach the old man to know whole grains
それは老人に自分のディナープレートを教えること、老人に全粒穀物について教えることです
we still have tea over there
あそこにはまだお茶があるよ
cultural promotion
文化促進
That is to say, I want him to drink tea again
つまり、もう一度お茶を飲んでもらいたいのです
I want him to drink milk again
また牛乳を飲ませたい
Then just make a milk tea culture
あとはミルクティー文化を作るだけです
or latte culture
ラテ文化とか
teach them how to make tea
彼らにお茶の入れ方を教える
And what are the desserts that go with the tea?
そしてお茶に合うデザートは何でしょうか？
It's like dried fruit, lotus fruit, etc.
ドライフルーツや蓮の実などです。
that's very healthy
それはとても健康的です
Take the milk and lotus fruit that they can't eat
彼らが食べられない牛乳と蓮の実を持って行ってください
eat it all
全部食べる
Some old people can't eat the fruits and vegetables
果物や野菜を食べられない高齢者もいます
How to eat it creatively
クリエイティブな食べ方
Of course, most young people will use some
もちろん、ほとんどの若者はいくつかを使用するでしょう
Fruit and vegetable juice, yogurt like this, these
果物や野菜のジュース、ヨーグルト、こんなもの
The old man may not be able to
老人にはそれができないかもしれない
What method does the old man use?
老人はどんな方法を使うのでしょうか？
For example, a situation in our family is
たとえば、私たちの家族の状況は次のとおりです。
my mother
私の母
My mother is a hundred years old now
私の母はもう百歳です
she is also very healthy
彼女もとても健康です
But she does eat less
しかし、彼女は食べる量が減りました
So for example, the day before she
たとえば、彼女の前日
If there are vegetables left over from lunch or dinner
昼食や夕食で野菜が残っている場合
then we'll collect it
それから私たちがそれを集めます
freeze it well
よく凍らせてください
For example, the next morning
例えば、翌朝、
i'll chop it up
私はそれを切り刻みます
then with an egg
それから卵で
turn into vegetable eggs
野菜の卵に変わる
Then put it on three sides of her
それからそれを彼女の三方に置きます
For example like this
たとえばこのように
Then you just make sure he gets the vegetables
あとは彼が野菜を確実に食べられるようにするだけです
will eat
食べる
This is an example
これは一例です
What about fruit?
果物はどうでしょうか？
That is my mother only
一日だけ私の母です
that appetite
その食欲
fruit that can only be eaten once
一度しか食べられない果物
He can't eat in the afternoon and evening
昼と夜は食べられない
So I must carry a bowl of fruit for him for breakfast
だから私は彼の朝食のためにフルーツ一杯を運ばなければなりません
that's it
それでおしまい
if i go home at noon
正午に家に帰ったら
I'll pour him a glass
彼にグラスを注いであげます
100 percent orange juice
100パーセントオレンジジュース
put on the table
テーブルの上に置く
He will see it when he wakes up at noon
彼は正午に目が覚めたらそれを見るでしょう
i'm busy
私は忙しいんだ
if i forget
忘れたら
i go home at night
夜には家に帰ります
Arrive home at half past five
5時半に家に到着
I'll pour a glass first
まずはグラスに注いでみます
100 percent orange juice
100パーセントオレンジジュース
or grape juice
またはブドウジュース
put it over there
そこに置いてください
just ask him to drink first
彼に最初に飲むように頼んでください
then wait until i make dinner
それから夕食を作るまで待ってください
that is to say
つまり
so-called creativity
いわゆる創造性
if you want
お望みならば
what can't be done
何ができないのか
there is
がある
View Breakfast for the Elderly
高齢者向け朝食を見る
this is very important
これはとても重要です
because the old and the young
なぜなら老人も若者も
The difference is that
違いは、
you young man can
若い君ならできるよ
I don't eat a meal
食事は食べません
then i have dinner or lunch
それから夕食か昼食を食べます
pile of protein
タンパク質の山
fill it up
埋めてください
then my body can take it
そうすれば私の体はそれを受け入れることができます
and I always
そして私はいつも
My muscle nuclear ability is all in
私の筋肉の核能力はすべて揃っています
But the old man did not eat this meal
しかし老人はこの食事を食べませんでした
He just lost that opportunity to do the synthesis of chicken
彼は鶏肉を合成する機会を失っただけだ
Therefore, what is important is that the elderly should eat protein from breakfast
したがって、高齢者は朝食からたんぱく質を摂取することが重要です。
Meal distribution
食事の配布
It is best to have vegetables, fruits and protein in all three meals
3食とも野菜、果物、たんぱく質を摂るのがベスト
ensure the metabolism of his body
彼の体の新陳代謝を確実にする
The synthesis of protein chicken is in the best state
鶏肉のタンパク質の合成は最高の状態にあります
so we have a moment that is old age breakfast
老後の朝食のひと時を過ごしましょう
Teach them how to eat breakfast and how to match it
朝食の食べ方と朝食の組み合わせ方を教える
This is a formula we promote in the community
これは私たちがコミュニティで推進している方式です
they still read
彼らはまだ読んでいます
I don't know if I click it
クリックしても分かりません
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
awesome
素晴らしい
ok this is right there
わかりました、ここはそこです
I've been working on this project for the past two years
私は過去 2 年間このプロジェクトに取り組んできました
The effect will not be known until the end of the year
効果は年末まで分からない
This weakness of these old people
この老人たちのこの弱さ
Is there any progress in all aspects?
あらゆる面で何か進歩はありますか？
OK, let me see the time
OK、時間を見てみましょう
It should be almost
ほぼそうなるはずです
So now let's talk about this website
それでは、このウェブサイトについて話しましょう
what about this website
このウェブサイトはどうですか
is if people want to know your own
人々があなた自身のことを知りたがっているかどうか
Six categories of book distribution
6つの書籍流通カテゴリー
you can in google
Googleでできます
I didn't leave the URL
URLを残していませんでした
You are in Google
あなたは Google にいます
Hit this Zhongyan Nutrition Information Website
Zhongyan の栄養情報 Web サイトにアクセスしてください
just hit this
これを叩くだけ
It will run out like this screen
この画面のように切れてしまいます
This picture is
この写真は
Just fill in your age here
ここにあなたの年齢を記入してください
your gender
あなたの性別
how tall are you
あなたの身長はどれくらいですか
how many kilograms
何キログラム
and your physical activity
そしてあなたの身体活動
It has low fever low moderately higher
微熱があり、中程度に高いです
make a choice
選択をする
Then here is the description
それでは説明です
who is low
誰が低いですか
who is low fever
微熱は誰ですか
For example, if you say low
たとえば、低いと言ったら、
This means most of the time
つまり、ほとんどの場合、
They all sit and study, do homework, and talk
彼らは皆座って勉強したり、宿題をしたり、話したりしています
Watch TV or listen to music part of the time
時々テレビを見たり音楽を聴いたりする
There is a small process of walking and other calorie consumption for an hour.
1時間のウォーキングやその他のカロリー消費という小さなプロセスがあります。
This one hour, for example, matching
この1時間、例えばマッチング
For example, if you walk to take the bus
たとえば、歩いてバスに乗る場合
then go home what
じゃあ家に帰って何
or walking around the house for about an hour
または家の周りを1時間ほど散歩する
So this is low
だからこれは低いんだよ
Then if the fever is low, it means
そうすると、熱が低いということは、
Except just like this
このようなことを除いて
There will be about two hours of walking
歩くと2時間くらいかかります
Then moderation means that in addition to the above
すると、節度というのは上記に加えて、
You still have an hour of vigorous work
まだ 1 時間の精力的な作業が残っています
or such a caloric expenditure
またはそのようなカロリー消費
An hour of activity at a fast pace
速いペースでの 1 時間のアクティビティ
Calorie-intensive activities
カロリー集約的な活動
For example, if you play ball for an hour
たとえば、1時間ボール遊びをしたとします。
this will be moderate
これは中程度でしょう
but every day
でも毎日
If you only call twice a week
週に2回しか電話をかけない場合
you're sick
あなたは病気です
this is every day
これは毎日です
If it is high, it means high-intensity activities every day.
値が高い場合は、毎日高強度のアクティビティを行っていることを意味します。
You probably look where you belong
あなたはおそらく自分の居場所を探しているでしょう
It will do a calculation for you
計算をしてくれます
Here the calculation would say
ここで計算すると、
how tall are you for a man
男性としてのあなたの身長はどれくらいですか
how much weight
体重はどれくらいですか
What is your BMI approximately?
あなたのBMIはおよそどれくらいですか?
Although you are normal now
今は普通なのに
but
しかし
i would suggest you
私はあなたに提案します
It is best to reach BMI22
BMI22に到達するのがベスト
That is, how much weight
つまり体重はどれくらいかというと、
at this weight
この体重で
Do you need 2099 calories a day
1日2099カロリー必要ですか
That's about 2100, right?
2100くらいですよね？
So there are two classes on this side
したがって、こちら側には 2 つのクラスがあります
tell you
教えてください
You're probably somewhere in between
あなたはおそらくその中間にいるでしょう
directly between the two
二人の間で直接
What kind of state is it?
どのような状態なのでしょうか？
is that you may eat every day
毎日食べてもいいということです
Three or three and a half bowls of rice
ご飯茶わん3～3杯半
divide by three
3で割る
just a bowl
ただのボウル
more bowls of rice
ご飯をもっと一杯
In this, I hope it means
これが意味することを願っています
at least one bowl is
少なくとも1つのボウルは
this
これ
No refinement is what is called
洗練されていないことをいわゆる
something like brown rice
玄米のようなもの
in this way
この上
Then you wish you every day
そしてあなたは毎日あなたを望んでいます
have a drink or two
一杯か二杯飲んでください
Just a cup and a half of milk
牛乳1カップ半だけ
Then your tofu
それからあなたの豆腐
About six servings of meat and eggs
肉と卵約6人分
The word six copies is the spacer I just mentioned
6 コピーという単語は、先ほど述べたスペーサーです。
Allocation of six like this
こんな感じで6個割り当て
You see it is assigned to three three
3 3 に割り当てられていることがわかります。
Four plates of vegetables
野菜4皿
Three to three and a half servings of fruit
フルーツ 3 ～ 3.5 サービング
6 servings of nut seeds
ナッツシード 6食分
This is more difficult to understand
これはさらにわかりにくいです
I can tell you about this
これについてお話しできます
What does it mean
どういう意味ですか
Just the nut seed that one of you has a serving of each day
ナッツの種を 1 日に 1 つ摂取するだけです
What does the remaining five mean?
残りの5つは何を意味するのでしょうか？
That is, you have five dishes in the four dishes every day
つまり毎日4品のうち5品が食べられるということです。
it is fried in oil
油で揚げたものです
So every day if you
だから毎日、もしあなたが
You see, four servings of vegetables are already four dishes.
ほら、野菜4人分ですでに4品になります。
And six servings of bean, fish, meat and eggs
豆、魚、肉、卵も6食分あります
there are ten
10個あります
that is to say
つまり
Not every dish is fried with oil
すべての料理が油で揚げられるわけではありません
half is good
半分でいいよ
For example, some of my fish today are steamed
たとえば、今日の魚の一部は蒸しています
some are fried
いくつかは揚げられています
fried with oil
油で揚げたもの
steamed without oil
油を使わずに蒸したもの
baked without oil
油を使わずに焼き上げた
If the vegetables are cold
野菜が冷めたら
no oil
油がありません
fried with oil
油で揚げたもの
so the dish you have is salad
それで、あなたが持っている料理はサラダです
some dishes are fried
いくつかの料理は揚げられています
some are hot
一部は暑いです
only half of the dish
料理の半分だけ
whether it is faint
かすかであるかどうか
Half of it is made of oil
半分は石油でできている
But that oil is not a restaurant
でもその油はレストランではありません
Let's go to the restaurant and order a dish
レストランに行って料理を注文しましょう
Isn't that the whole dish soaked in oil?
お皿全体に油が染み込んでいませんか？
it's not like that
そんなことはない
It's almost the oil level of a buffet
ほぼビュッフェの油レベルです
I know only half is oily
半分だけが油っぽいことを知ってください
Then your oil level is just right.
そうすれば、オイルレベルは適切になります。
some people are healthy
健康な人もいる
No cooking oil
食用油は使用しないでください
no no no way
いやいや、まさか
then you can be at your healthiest
そうすればあなたは最も健康でいられます
It is your six servings that all use Heguo seeds
和果種子を使用した6食分です。
The most important thing is that it is possible
最も重要なことはそれが可能であるということです
Every dish of yours is a salad
あなたの料理はすべてサラダです
Your salad is hot
あなたのサラダは温かいです
this can also
これもできます
So these are where the creativity
ここで創造性が発揮されます
good so
いいですね
Speaking of this
これについて言えば
I think it's about the same time
ほぼ同じ時期だと思います
It's about ninety minutes
90分くらいですよ
right
右
May I
いいですか
thank you very much
どうもありがとうございます
Ask Professor Han's very informative lecture
ハン教授の非常に有益な講義を聞く
then we now
それから私たちは今
ask questions
質問をする
If you ask this question, we will give you a copy
この質問をしていただければコピーを差し上げます
I think it's a magazine for scientists.
科学者向けの雑誌だと思います。
Thank you all for asking
ご質問いただきありがとうございます
So another one can do
それで、別の人ができるのは、
Thank you, Professor Pan, for your in-depth introduction.
パン教授、詳しい紹介をありがとうございました。
I want to ask Professor Pan
パン先生に聞きたい
That is to say, on page 18 of your talk about Bubbles just now
つまり、今のバブルの話の 18 ページにあります。
After the so-called old people there are weak
いわゆる老人の後には弱者がいる
His activity decreased, his diet decreased
活動性が低下し、食事も減少した
it's a vicious circle
それは悪循環です
Ask Professor Pan
パン教授に聞く
It's the English part
英語の部分です
The professor just mentioned that
先ほど教授がおっしゃいました
It is hoped to increase the activity and amount of exercise of the elderly
高齢者の活動量や運動量の向上が期待されます。
to stimulate his appetite to increase his diet
食欲を刺激して食事を増やす
to break the cycle
サイクルを断ち切るために
but if say
でも言うなら
Our caregivers fall into a myth
私たちの介護者は神話に陥っています
just say it's because you're unlucky
それはあなたが運が悪いからだと言ってください
So I use forced fasting
そこで私は強制断食をします
Just use bio fasting, forced fasting
バイオ断食、強制断食を利用するだけです
I cut off so much in a row
連続でたくさん切りました
People can't break this cycle when it's like this
このような状況では人はこのサイクルを断ち切ることができません
i will ask several questions
いくつか質問させていただきます
so my first question
それで私の最初の質問
let the professor answer
教授に答えてもらいましょう
Then I ask the second question
次に2番目の質問をします
I'll ask another question when I get a chance
機会があればまた質問させていただきます
Thanks
ありがとう
by force
力ずくで
Because I personally don't recommend
個人的にはオススメしないので
But none of us did either
しかし、私たちの誰もそのどちらもしませんでした
It's just that I didn't pay attention to whether there is such a test
そんなテストがあるかどうか気にしていなかっただけです
what if there is no test
テストがなかったらどうなるか
It's not good to say it's impossible
無理って言うのは良くないよ
But that is to say, if you analyze a state where the elderly cannot eat
しかし、つまり、高齢者が食べられない状態を分析すると、
It eats so little that it can't eat it
食べる量が少なすぎて食べられない
space in its stomach
お腹の中のスペース
It doesn't have enough digestion for anything
何に対しても消化力が足りない
so in this case
したがってこの場合は
I believe in forced fasting
私は強制断食を信じています
May have some adverse effects
何らかの悪影響がある可能性があります
so of course i
だからもちろん私は
Because we didn't enter into such a trial
私たちはそのような裁判には参加していないので、
Can't eat the old man
老人は食べられない
As long as there is a group, it is forced
集団がある限り強制される
so i'm having a hard time
だから私は苦労しています
Indeed, your question is really difficult
確かにあなたの質問は本当に難しいです
hard to answer
答えるのが難しい
but we know that
しかし私たちはそれを知っています
When the old man can't eat
おじいさんが食べられなくなったら
If you force him to eat, he will feel uncomfortable
無理に食べさせると不快に感じるでしょう
Because we're talking about aging now
今は老化の話をしているから
So the stroke after aging
つまり、加齢後の脳卒中
what those radar teams
あのレーダーチームは何だ
Then he will swallow
そうすれば彼は飲み込むだろう
But we often meet evildoers and say
しかし、私たちはしばしば悪者に会い、こう言います。
Then I just have to wait for the break, after the break
あとは休憩を待つだけです、休憩が終わったら
He can live for several years
彼は数年は生きることができる
just lie there
ただそこに横たわってください
Just lay there and live for several years.
ただそこに横たわって何年も生きてください。
So the myth here goes like this
ここでの神話は次のようになります
That's why I asked this question
だからこそこの質問をしたのです
But what I would suggest is to say
しかし、私が提案したいのは、
I just said break
休憩って言っただけだよ
not in this way
この方法ではなく
break means
休憩手段
For example, we are in Miaoli Hospital
たとえば、私たちは苗栗病院にいます。
we'll find out now
今すぐわかるよ
What's wrong with these old men's reclining strength?
この老人たちのリクライニングの強さはどうしたの？
we designed some
私たちはいくつかをデザインしました
easy exercise for him
彼のための簡単な運動
he started doing it
彼はそれをやり始めた
when he first did
彼が初めてやったとき
his physical exertion
彼の肉体労働
he will start to want to eat
彼は食べたくなるでしょう
I think this is a
これは
smarter way
より賢い方法
and you
あなたも
you change the quality of food
あなたは食べ物の質を変えます
you can design
あなたはデザインすることができます
This food is more dance-like
この食べ物はもっとダンスっぽいです
That is to say, it uses a small volume
つまり使用量が少ない
it won't last
それは続かないでしょう
eat that nutrition
その栄養を食べる
These two methods will
これら 2 つの方法は、
I think it will be better
もっと良くなると思います
the next page
次のページ
The so-called protein American gluten body weight
いわゆるプロテインアメリカングルテンの体重
Calculation standard of the body weight of the American gluten
アメリカングルテンの体重の計算基準
based on its current weight
現在の体重に基づいて
Or ideal weight ID28 Liwet
または理想体重 ID28 Liwet
still have to count the weight
まだ体重を数えなければなりません
Lin8 Liwet
リン８・リウェット
dimensional basis to calculate its heavy protein requirement
重タンパク質の必要量を計算するための寸法ベース
Thanks
ありがとう
This is now internationally
これはもう国際的に
Usually the current weight
通常は現在の体重
We are also useful Lin8 LiMes
私たちも便利なLin8 LiMes
also counted
もカウントされます
basically the same one
基本的に同じものです
same trend
同じ傾向
but this is currently
しかし、これは現在
Currently because it is in this clinical
現在この臨床中のため
more useful method
より便利な方法
It is directly minus the weight
直接体重をマイナスしたものです
I understand that you should fully understand this question
この質問を十分に理解する必要があることを理解しています
Is you considering Lin8 LiMes
Lin8 LiMes を検討していますか
body mass may be more important
体重の方が重要かもしれない
all good questions
すべての良い質問
Many thanks to Yuan Pan for the report
Yuan Pan さんのレポートに感謝します
Then I want to say that in this life
じゃあ、この人生で言いたいのは
It is the history of birth and disease
誕生と病気の歴史です
come here to eat such good food
こんなおいしいものを食べるためにここに来てください
Until the last nine years old and one hundred years old, they are all gone
9歳まで、100歳まで
I want to take advantage of your report
あなたのレポートを活用したい
do an extended role
拡張された役割をする
The question until that day is
その日までの疑問は、
stop breathing
停止呼吸
that problem is too big
その問題は大きすぎます
I want to extend that
それを拡張したい
by Namoban
透過Namoban
Scarmorivo
スカルモリボ
there's a world we can go to
私たちが行ける世界がある
is the brightest world
最も明るい世界です
life is infinite
人生は無限です
That is to say, the Western Paradise
つまり西方極楽浄土
Amitabha
阿弥陀
So the theory starts out pretty big
理論はかなり壮大なことから始まります
it's not oriental
それは東洋的ではありません
it is a science
それは科学です
great knowledge
素晴らしい知識
So Master Xuanzang traveled from Xi'an to India during the Tang Dynasty
そこで、玄奘先生は唐の時代に西安からインドへ旅行しました。
It took a few years to arrive
届くまでに数年かかりました
It took a total of 17 years to return from studying in India
インド留学から帰国まで計17年かかった
He has brought back many life theories of Buddhist managers
彼は仏教経営者の多くの人生論を持ち帰りました。
Like what Wu Liang said, the Diamond Sutra and so on
呉良の言ったこと、『金剛経』など
very great experience
とても素晴らしい経験
then these classics
それからこれらの古典
Then everyone can solve their own problems
そうすれば誰もが自分の問題を解決できる
Meet your long-term needs
長期的なニーズにお応えします
That is to say, watch these classics on TV
つまり、これらの古典作品をテレビで見てください
Then there are many mages like Jing Kong mage
それから、Jing Kong mageのような多くのmageがいます
Master Haitao came to help us explain
ハイタオ先生が説明を手伝ってくれました
Only when a mage explains it can we understand
魔術師が説明して初めて理解できる
There's such a wonderful world we can go to
私たちが行ける素晴らしい世界がある
I believe that many people here have learned Amitabha
ここには阿弥陀仏を学んだ人がたくさんいると思います
Then another question
それから別の質問
Our research unit is studying this excellent
私たちの研究ユニットはこの素晴らしいことを研究しています
At this time, is there any religion or the Buddhist law I just talked about?
この時、先ほど話した宗教や仏法はありますか？
Introduced to study how to solve outstanding problems
未解決の問題の解決方法を学ぶために導入されました
then i will share
それから私は共有します
If you encounter excellent
素晴らしいものに出会ったら
forget about that now
もうそのことは忘れてください
Immediately transform the new realm into
新しい領域をすぐに変換します
Amitabha
阿弥陀
so new is close
新しいものが近いです
there is no such thing
そのようなことはない
Thank you Amitabha
阿弥陀さま、ありがとう
ok thank you for sharing
わかりました、共有してくれてありがとう
let's see if
どうか見てみましょう
who has some questions
何か問題を抱えている人は
Excuse me
すみません
That is what the professor just mentioned
それが今先生がおっしゃったことです
proper food and drink
適切な食べ物と飲み物
tea coffee
紅茶コーヒー
even the so-called wine
いわゆるワインでさえ
suggested by the professor
教授が提案した
the so-called appropriate amount
いわゆる適量
what is the appropriate amount
適切な量​​はどれくらいですか
that's it
それでおしまい
so-called tea coffee
いわゆるティーコーヒー
Even wine, red wine, etc.
ワインや赤ワインなどでも構いません。
the so-called appropriate amount
いわゆる適量
because of coffee
コーヒーのせいで
is what we know to say
それは私たちが知っていることです
When doing volume
ボリュームを出すときは
would cause the so-called
いわゆる
stop loss stop neglect
ストップロスストップ無視
that's again
それはまたです
other deteriorating part of debilitating
衰弱の他の悪化部分
That's why the professor suggested
そこで教授が提案したのが、
the so-called appropriate amount
いわゆる適量
Then it's protein
それからプロテインです
Can't talk about the so-called milk powder, right?
いわゆる粉ミルクの話はできないですよね？
Milk powder is a remanufactured product
粉ミルクは再生品です
That milk powder and the so-called fresh milk
その粉ミルクといわゆる生乳
It's in making this about our nutrition
私たちの栄養についてこれを作ることです
Is there a difference in the scenery difference?
景色の違いに違いはあるのでしょうか？
Thanks
ありがとう
because we are today
私たちは今日だから
discuss this issue
この問題について話し合う
it has a bit of what it should say
言うべきことが少し含まれています
is that it is a political
それは政治的なものであるということです
Because it this food is a
なぜなら、この食べ物は、
very complicated thing
とても複雑なこと
it can't be like a
のようなことはできません
so-called basic research
所謂基礎研究
That is to say one thing at a time
つまり、一度に一つのことを言うのです
because it is very complicated
とても複雑なので
So we usually when making recommendations
したがって、私たちは通常、提案をするときに
from this information
この情報から
see what can be seen
何が見えるかを見る
let's make suggestions
提案をしましょう
that is to say it is not easy
つまりそれは簡単ではない
so-called heterodyne
所謂的外差
Or extend up and down
もしくは上下に伸ばすか
Then when I was looking at our profile
それでプロフィールを見ていたところ、
I find
見つけました
The so-called group that eats a lot like tea
いわゆるお茶のようにたくさん食べる派
in this way
この上
it is about
それは約です
so the coffee is over there
それならそのコーヒーはあそこにあります
Taiwanese people eat less coffee after all
台湾人は結局コーヒーをあまり食べない
Its relevance is like this
関連性はこんな感じです
coffee is usually
コーヒーは通常
These chitons are just two or three cups a week
これらのキトンは週にわずか 2 ～ 3 杯です
But the tea is almost drunk to a cup a day
でもお茶は1日1杯くらいしか飲まない
So now I can say that
だから今だから言えるのは
Based on our current political observation
現在の政治的見解に基づいて
the state of this crowd
この群衆の様子
Looks like a cup of tea a day would be nice
一日一杯のお茶がいいそうですよ
and I think the main effect
そして私が思う主な効果は
probably from tea
おそらくお茶から
because it is a pattern
それはパターンだから
it is relevant
それは関連しています
But you will see that there is still less coffee in that range
しかし、その範囲内ではコーヒーの量がまだ少ないことがわかります。
I don't know if Taiwanese really
本当に台湾人なのかは分からない
When Westerners drink so much coffee
西洋人がコーヒーを飲みすぎると
what will happen
何が起こるか
So I must say that when I was talking about this thing today
だから、今日このことについて話しているときに言わなければなりません
I think it depends on your personal physique
個人の体格にもよると思いますが、
But if I want to promote this thing
でもこれを宣伝したいなら
I will focus on tea
お茶に集中していきます
Because it is more tea
もっとお茶なので
this is your first question
これがあなたの最初の質問です
as for a little more
もう少しについては
I believe there is no problem
問題ないと信じています
as long as you are drinking
飲んでいる限り
I still feel that the body can adapt
まだ体が適応できる気がする
Like some people the coffee is good though
一部の人たちと同じように、コーヒーはおいしいですが
but some people can't drink coffee
でもコーヒーが飲めない人もいる
can't drink
飲めない
basically
基本上
just because it's a
それはただ
how to say
どのように言って
This is Observation
これは観察です
is a human
人間です
Natural Experiments
自然実験
a thing of nature experiment
自然の実験
So we can't go beyond it too much
だからそれをあまり超えることはできない
so this is the first question
これが最初の質問です
I just forgot the second one
2つ目は忘れてた
milk powder
粉ミルク
Yeah
うん
this is indeed
これは確かに
A fresh milk has this structure of this protein
新鮮な牛乳はこのタンパク質の構造を持っています
with milk powder
粉ミルク入り
because milk powder
粉ミルクだから
put moisture like this
こうやって水分を入れて
evaporate
蒸発する
Its structure is indeed different
確かに構造が違いますね
but i must say
しかし、言わなければなりません
I because I am studying nutrition training
私は栄養トレーニングの勉強をしているので
We usually focus on nutrition
私たちは通常、栄養に重点を置いています
The problem with this structure involves
この構造の問題点は次のとおりです。
This immune allergy
この免疫アレルギーは
It's not my major
それは私の専攻ではありません
but we found
しかし、私たちは見つけました
That is to say, in nutrition
つまり栄養学では
milk powder and fresh milk
粉ミルクと生乳
It seems that there is not much difference
あまり差が無いように思えますが
that is
あれは
For protein intake
プロテイン摂取に
calcium intake
カルシウム摂取量
So if it is beyond this range
したがって、この範囲を超える場合は、
of
の
When it comes to allergies, it's not my field.
アレルギーに関しては私の専門外です。
But I feel there is no difference in nutrition
でも栄養的には大差ない気がする
You said you have to walk steadily, right?
しっかり歩かなければいけないって言いましたよね？
oh
おお
Weak feet will fall
足が弱いと倒れてしまいます
In fact, I believe there are many reasons
実際には、たくさんの理由があると思います
But if you're talking about what we're talking about today
でも、今日私たちが話していることについて話しているのであれば、
this debilitating word of encouragement
この弱気になる励ましの言葉
that big problem
その大きな問題
OK, what we are talking about today is the issue of motivation
さて、今日私たちが話しているのはモチベーションの問題です
Because you see the protein I talked about today
今日話したタンパク質が見えるからです
There is also protein, which is a raw material for muscle synthesis
筋肉合成の原料となるたんぱく質もあります
Then we mentioned that fruits and vegetables are anti-inflammatory
次に、果物と野菜には抗炎症作用があると述べました
We all know why old people talk to young people
なぜ老人が若者に話しかけるのかは誰もが知っています
Eat the same protein but your muscle synthesis doesn't
同じたんぱく質を食べても筋肉合成は行われない
It's because your body is in a state of inflammation
体が炎症を起こしているからです
Your synthesis side is weaker
合成側が弱い
Therefore, there must be antioxidant
したがって、抗酸化物質が必要です
It will be better if it is provided together with protein
プロテインと一緒に摂るとさらに良いですね
But if a person is already weak enough
しかし、その人がすでに十分に弱っている場合、
It must be paired with exercise
運動と組み合わせる必要があります
is that you have to match some breaks
いくつかの区切りを一致させる必要があるということです
so in this
それでこれで
We're in the middle of this Selary study
私たちはセラリーの研究の真っ最中です
We have four types of sports
4種類のスポーツをご用意しております
The middle one is muscle strength
真ん中は筋力です
Main resistance exercise, strength training and stretching exercise
主な抵抗運動、筋力トレーニング、ストレッチ運動
There are soft exercises and aerobic
ソフトな運動と有酸素運動があります
all four
4つすべて
Then there are upper and lower limbs
あとは上肢と下肢です
There are such sports
こんなスポーツもあるんですね
so if you
それで、もしあなたが
Your weakness is not due to structural problems
あなたの弱点は構造的な問題によるものではありません
or neurological problems
または神経学的問題
If the muscles are weak
筋肉が弱いと
You should start to practice the underhand
アンダーハンドの練習を始めるべきです
some movement in the lower body
下半身の動き
including things like squats
スクワットなども含めて
Then ask a sports coach
それからスポーツコーチに聞いてください
can be practiced
実践できる
But light nutrition is not enough
しかし、軽度の栄養では十分ではありません
big problem you tell him
あなたが彼に言う大きな問題
Any question
ご質問は何でも
yes
はい
please
お願いします
black tea
茶有紅茶
green tea
緑茶
yes
はい
There are black tea and green tea, right?
紅茶と緑茶がありますよね？
What about green tea?
緑茶はどうでしょうか？
pure green tea
純粋な緑茶
and light green tea
そして薄緑茶
that black tea
あの紅茶
some are grape tea
一部はブドウ茶です
So black tea is better?
じゃあ紅茶のほうがいいの？
Is green tea better?
緑茶の方が良いのでしょうか？
In terms of nutrition and moisture
栄養と水分の面では
no difference
変わりはない
because
なぜなら
because i should say the same
私も同じことを言うべきだから
It is because of our research
それは私たちの研究のおかげです
This is an epidemiological study
これは疫学調査です
If you really want me to divide it so finely
そんなに細かく分けて欲しいなら
I have no way
仕方が無い
So I see from our data that
データからわかることは、
no difference
変わりはない
But I believe there must be some
でもきっといくつかあると思うよ
slight difference
わずかな違い
But that difference is
しかし、その違いは、
I can't answer today
今日は答えられない
there's still something like that
まだそんな事あるの
vitamin c problem
ビタミンCの問題
So why isn't vitamin C a problem?
では、なぜビタミンCは問題にならないのでしょうか?
It is because people in Taiwan
それは台湾の人たちだから
Your Designated Amount of Vitamin C
指定量のビタミンC
It has reached two or three hundred times your daily demand
それは1日の需要量の200～300倍に達しています
you know we do research
私たちが研究をしていることを知っていますか
just doesn't matter
ただ関係ない
high is okay
高くても大丈夫です
but that means we are
しかしそれは私たちがいるということです
go go go
已經go go go
us
私たち
But that doesn't mean
しかし、それは意味がありません
You can't take vitamin C supplements
ビタミンCのサプリメントは摂取できない
it's two different things
それは2つの異なるものです
So I think the vitamin C thing is relatively small
だからビタミンCは比較的少ないと思います
Then the advantages of this check
次に、このチェックの利点
Definitely not only in this flesh-wrestling disease
間違いなく、この肉のレスリングの病気だけではありません
Like our market and do some other research
私たちの市場を気に入って、他の調査をしてください
like ever done i did npc bni
これまでのように私はnpc bniをしました
Diet Patterns for BNI
BNI の食事パターン
An intermediate protective factor is to check
真ん中の保護要素はチェックです
Then I have the impression that all kinds of checks are protected
それから、あらゆるチェックが守られているような印象を持ちます。
Cha is really a very good
チャさんは本当に上手いよ
Various chronic life
各種慢性命
It has a preventive effect
予防効果があります
contains cancer
がんが含まれている
the teacher has another question
先生は別の質問があります
usually when drinking tea
たいていお茶を飲むとき
drink tea like me
私のようにお茶を飲みます
Because I have been drinking tea for about twenty years
20年くらいお茶を飲み続けているので
I don't dare to drink tea so far
今のところお茶を飲む勇気はない
why
なぜ
After drinking, there will often be a phenomenon of willingness
飲酒後は、意欲が湧く現象がよく起こります。
Is it the same with drinking coffee?
コーヒーを飲むときも同じでしょうか？
No coffee should be no
コーヒーはダメであってはなりません
Coffee should be an opposite in this piece
この作品ではコーヒーは対極であるべきです
Because there are some other minerals in coffee
コーヒーには他のミネラルも含まれているので、
it will help you have a bowel movement
排便を助けるでしょう
So I don't want to be constipated by tea
だからお茶で便秘になりたくない
we are other
私たちは他人です
we don't have this experience
私たちにはこの経験がありません
Maybe this is a condition of a constitution that varies from person to person
これは人によって異なる体質なのかもしれません
yes
はい
there is one behind
後ろに1人います
Excuse me
すみません
You have contributed here says
あなたはここに貢献しました
The fourth said the anti-inflammatory food
4番目は抗炎症作用のある食べ物と言った
I want to ask about the sweets
お菓子について聞きたいのですが
Will it make that body inflamed?
その体が炎症を起こすでしょうか？
Sweets are an inflammatory food
甘いものは炎症を起こす食べ物です
Yes
はい
What are anti-inflammatory foods
抗炎症食品とは何ですか
Anti-inflammatory foods we usually are
私たちが普段摂取している抗炎症食品
fruits and vegetables
果物と野菜
It is absolutely anti-inflammatory
完全に抗炎症作用があります
then again
また
like fish
魚のように
picture
像
this piece of oil
この油片
fat part
脂肪部分
that is, every type of food
つまりあらゆる種類の食べ物
can talk like this
このように話すことができます
I just said that the first one is vegetables and fruits
最初は野菜と果物だと言いました
anti-inflammatory
抗炎症薬
So what about fat?
脂肪はどうですか？
saturation
飽和
Unsaturated
不飽和
and
と
this
これ
just how to say
ちょうどどのように言うか
As for the oil, it tends to be plant-based
油に関しては植物由来のものが多い
vegetable oil
植物油
Then
それから
with fish oil
魚油入り
But what about vegetable oil and fish oil?
では、植物油や魚油はどうでしょうか？
Is fish oil more anti-inflammatory
魚油は抗炎症作用が強いですか
But fish oil probably can't eat too much like this
でも魚油はこんなふうにたくさん食べられないかもしれない
mean to say
言う意味
In terms of general sneezing oil
一般的なくしゃみ油に関して
we lean towards vegetable oil
私たちは植物油に傾いています
But if the vegetable oil says
しかし、植物油が言うなら、
olive oil
オリーブオイル
canola oil
キャノーラ油
and these soybean oils
そしてこの大豆油は
In other words, olive oil is the only advantage
言い換えれば、オリーブオイルだけが利点です
Another advantage because it is more antioxidant
抗酸化作用が高いというもう一つの利点
What about soybean oil?
大豆油はどうでしょうか？
If you use stir-fried salad
炒めサラダを使う場合
The use of these methods is also ok
これらの方法を使ってもOKです
But that soybean oil
でもその大豆油は
sunflower oil these if used at high temperature
高温で使用する場合はひまわり油
it is less inflammatory
炎症が少ないです
It's a little bit complicated, it's a little bit complicated
それは少し複雑です、それは少し複雑です
Good cleanser oils are very inflammatory
優れたクレンザーオイルは非常に炎症を起こしやすい
absolutely can't eat
絶対に食べられない
Now Qinghuayou government has legislated
現在、清華佑政府は法律を制定しました
take it out of food
食べ物から取り出す
It has been in law for almost three years
法律が制定されてからほぼ3年が経ちます
It should be three years
3年になるはずだ
That is, after three years, high-speed manufacturers
つまり、3 年後には高速メーカーが
A complete ban is probably the closest
おそらく完全禁止が最も近いだろう
Three years ago, it was enacted that no cleaning oil should be used
3年前、洗浄油を使用しないことが制定されました
to the limit of hell
地獄の限界まで
Then I see I don't know yet
そうすると、まだ分からないことがわかりました
What did not expect is basically oil
予想外だったのは基本的にオイルです
Vegetables and fruits are the most important
野菜と果物が一番大事
Teacher, I beg
先生、お願いします
During your research, you mentioned that it was
調査中に、次のように述べられました。
body mass and muscle mass
体重と筋肉量
The amount of brittle falls in old age of boys is much more serious than that of girls
男児の老年期における脆性転倒の量は女児よりもはるかに深刻である
yes
はい
What is the mechanism that causes men to have this situation?
男性がこのような状態になってしまうメカニズムとは一体どのようなものなのでしょうか？
OK
OK
we all know men
私たちは皆、男性を知っています
That is to say, his aging process is actually
つまり、彼の老化プロセスは実際には
The aging process that has been going on since growing up is in progress
大人になってからの老化現象が進行中
What about women?
女性はどうですか？
Generally speaking, it is women because of the protective effect of female hormones
女性ホルモンの保護作用により、一般的には女性です。
So before a woman's menopause
つまり、女性の閉経前には
Basically, various chronic disease indicators are in a very good state
基本的に、さまざまな慢性疾患の指標は非常に良好な状態にあります
Women don't see this chronic disease take off until after menopause
女性は閉経後までこの慢性疾患が治りません
So women can be said to be later than men
つまり女性は男性より遅いと言えます
It can be said that it has been like this for decades
何十年もこのままだと言える
So when we look at various indicators, we can see such a phenomenon
さまざまな指標を見てみると、このような現象が見られます。
For example, female obesity
例えば女性の肥満
Women's gut ratings all take off after the age of fifty
女性の腸の評価は50歳を過ぎると急激に高まる
Then later rushed to be taller than boys
その後、男の子よりも背が高くなりました
Men have rushed to a peak after the age of seventy and all come down
男性は70歳を過ぎると一気にピークに達し、全員が下降してしまう
But that's down because of aging, not because of getting better
でもそれは老化のせいで、良くなったからではない
So basically it's a female hormone protection
基本的には女性ホルモンの保護です
should be the biggest reason
それが最大の理由のはず
Hello, Teacher Pan, your main thing is nutrition, right?
こんにちは、パン先生、あなたの主なことは栄養ですよね？
Then let me ask you about a nutritional therapy and nutritional repair in the future.
次に、今後の栄養療法と栄養修復について伺います。
What is the progress in China and what breakthroughs have been made?
中国ではどのような進歩があり、どのような進歩があったのでしょうか?
Your problem is very, very big
あなたの問題はとてもとても大きいです
feel a little bit about breakthrough we can
私たちができる突破口について少し感じてください
Maybe we can chat a bit later
たぶん、少し後でチャットできるでしょう
Because nutrition is really, really complicated
栄養学は本当に本当に複雑だから
There are many other aspects. What I am talking about today is the positive aspects of old age.
他にもたくさんの側面がありますが、今日私が話しているのは、老後のポジティブな側面です。
so i'm having a hard time answering
だから答えるのに困っている
because of baby nutrition
赤ちゃんの栄養のせいで
nutrition for pregnant women
妊婦のための栄養
Have nutrition for the elderly
高齢者向けの栄養を摂る
Chronic Disease Nutrition
慢性疾患の栄養
Disease prevention and treatment with cancer
生殖がんを伴う疾患の予防と治療
and disease treatment
そして病気の治療
many facets
多くの側面
so i can't answer right now
だから今は答えられない
do you have any specific questions
具体的な質問はありますか
Teacher Pan
パン先生
You seem to be on the heart side
あなたはハート側にいるようです
full of a heart weary even
心は満たされていても疲れていても
no large system
大規模なシステムはありません
A repair and therapy for noodles
麺の修復と治療
most importantly
最も重要なこと
Presentation of one of its research results
研究成果の一つを発表
If you come to the country where you are from now
今から来た国に来たら
what better way
何か良い方法はありますか
for example
例えば
like my heart
私の心のように
There is a problem caused by
原因となる問題があります
A functional underground of the pretend line
フリルラインの機能的なアンダーグラウンド
The function of the pretend line is underground
ふり回線の機能は地下にあります
I am nourishing myself
自分自身に栄養を与えている
Absorptive capacity
吸収量
a factor of the missing part
欠落部分の要因
Does it affect the heart?
心臓に影響はありますか？
even affect the kidneys
腎臓にも影響を与える
Yes or no
はい、もしくは、いいえ
nutritional therapy
栄養療法
Current Domestic Research
現在の国内研究
is there any progress
何か進展はありますか
i don't know
わからない
terribly sorry
大変申し訳ありません
because
なぜなら
assume this
これを仮定します
that pseudogland
その偽腺
because we generally
なぜなら私たちは一般的に
adenopathy in the largest
最大のリンパ節腫脹
it involves
それは含まれます
canned bean disease
缶詰の豆の病気
Then you just
それならあなたはただ
is the so-called
いわゆる
called secondary
二次と呼ばれる
that is because
それはなぜですか
caused by other diseases
他の病気が原因の場合
It actually has a lot to do with nutrition
実は栄養と大きく関係しているのです
Relatively far
比較遠
because I do nutrition
栄養補給してるから
close like a can
缶のように閉じる
that arterial
その動脈
this heart disease
この心臓病
is the largest
は最もおおきい
it involves
それは含まれます
diet
飲食
Fat
脂肪
Metabolic abnormalities
代謝異常
with diabetes
糖尿病を患っている
this metabolic abnormality
この代謝異常
The main thing is this
主なものはこれです
cause me in this
これで私が原因です
But the one you just said
でも、あなたが今言ったのは、
not my research scope
私の研究範囲ではありません
sorry sorry
ごめんごめん
see if there is anything else
他に何かあるかどうか見てください
other questions
その他の質問
and you just mentioned that
そしてあなたは今それについて言及しました
when boys
男の子のとき
when the whole recession
全体が不景気になったとき
waning from the start
最初から衰退している
but i used to
でも私は以前は
The information given to us is that the girl is after menopause
私たちに与えられた情報は、少女は閉経後であるということです
The speed of the entire recession will grow very fast
不況全体の速度は非常に早くなるだろう
But just now when the teacher made this information
でも今、先生がこの情報を出したとき
When the girl was at the time of the decaying speed
少女が減衰速度の頃だった頃
Much slower than boys
男の子よりもずっと遅い
What direction is this looking at?
これはどの方向を見ているのでしょうか？
One of the worst things women do have is osteoporosis
女性にとって最悪の病気の一つは骨粗鬆症です
Women lose bone very quickly after menopause
女性は閉経後すぐに骨を失います
She is indeed presenting an immediate drop
彼女は確かに即時低下を示しています
This is one of the most serious problems for women
これは女性にとって最も深刻な問題の一つです
men won't
男性はしません
males are slowly declining
男性は徐々に減ってきている
But what I just talked about is the other aspects
しかし、私が今話したのは他の側面です
especially metabolic like diabetes
特に糖尿病のような代謝
like a heart attack
心臓発作のような
like high blood pressure
高血圧のような
This piece of women starts after menopause
この女性の作品は閉経後に始まります
deterioration
劣化
But a woman is actually saying that she has a long time ahead
でも女性は実際には、まだまだ先は長いと言っている
It doesn't matter if the protection period starts at the beginning
保護期間が最初から始まっても問題ありません
It is very important for women to stop menstruation
女性にとって生理を止めることはとても大切です
Make drastic lifestyle adjustments now
今すぐライフスタイルを大幅に調整しましょう
It will be pressed back
押し戻されてしまいます
So it's fine for women too
なので女性でも大丈夫ですよ
It's because you suddenly discovered how my body changed
私の体の変化をあなたが突然発見したからです
If something is wrong, change immediately
何かが間違っている場合は、すぐに変更してください
If you want a big change, you can suppress it
大きな変化が必要な場合は、それを抑制できます
So yes lifestyle therapy has its uses
はい、ライフスタイル療法には用途があります
Excuse me, teacher, you just kept emphasizing
すみません、先生、ずっと強調してましたね
All Protein Milk Eggs
オールプロテインミルク・卵
But when we eat protein
しかし、プロテインを摂取すると、
acid in the stomach
胃の中の酸
PH3 is all denatured
PH3はすべて変性しています
Can it be used by our body again?
再び私たちの体で利用できるのでしょうか？
Transgender broke or what?
トランスジェンダーは破産しましたか？
is not like this
これはそうではありません
It is actually a process of digestion
それは実際には消化のプロセスです
What we eat is protein
私たちが食べているものはたんぱく質です
Proteins are many amino acids
タンパク質はアミノ酸がたくさん入ったものです
formed long sword
形成された長剣
So the long acid digestion in the stomach
したがって、胃の中で長い酸消化が行われます。
is very important
はとても重要です
because in that situation
なぜならその状況では
break down some proteins
一部のタンパク質を分解する
will put this long chain
この長いチェーンを付けます
The so-called ecology cut it off
いわゆるエコロジーがそれを切り取った
cut into tiny amino acids
小さなアミノ酸に切る
we can absorb
私たちは吸収できる
Without this action
このアクションがなければ
In fact, those proteins can't be absorbed
実はこれらのタンパク質は吸収されません
so it's not like you might think
だからそれはあなたが思っているようなことではない
Say it breaks, it ain't breaks
壊れると言うが、壊れていない
its destruction is called
その破壊はと呼ばれます
should be called decomposition
分解と言うべきか
break down from large molecules to small molecules
大きな分子から小さな分子に分解する
So we can take advantage of the absorbed
したがって、吸収されたものを活用できます
recombine in our body
私たちの体内で再結合する
Become an ecological long chain
環境に優しいロングチェーンになる
in the necessary position
必要な位置に
emerge with the necessary structure
必要な構造を備えて出現する
that transgender is not
トランスジェンダーはそうではない
like that us
そのように私たち
eggs to fry
揚げる卵
become hard
硬くなる
that is transgender
それはトランスジェンダーです
the same with stomach acid
胃酸も同様
also transgender
トランスジェンダーでもある
that ruined the whole
それは全体を台無しにした
no no no
ダメダメダメ
That's what it means to change sex
性転換とはそういうことだ
That is, it is in an animal or plant body
つまり動物や植物の体内にある
form of existence
存在の形
Then after you pass through the Lord
そして、主を通った後、
already transsexual
すでに性転換者
For example, protein white is liquid
例えばプロテインホワイトは液体です
Mainly will become solid
主に固体になります
The three-dimensional space of its structure changes
その構造の三次元空間が変化する
The three-dimensional space has changed
三次元空間が変わった
Then after you enter this body
そして、あなたがこの体に入った後、
No matter how it is three-dimensional space
たとえそれが三次元空間であっても
i cut it off
私はそれを切り落としました
It's the protein breaker cup
プロテインブレーカーカップです
cut it all off
全部切り落として
Cut it all into one tiny unit
すべてを 1 つの小さな単位にカットします
So whether transgender or not
つまり、トランスジェンダーであろうがなかろうが、
just eat your eggs
卵だけ食べてください
Or eat your already solid egg
または、すでに固まった卵を食べるか
It looks the same until it is decomposed
分解するまでは同じに見える
They are all small one by one
一つ一つは小さいものばかりですが、
just one by one
ひとつひとつだけ
Then the inside grows long enough to absorb it
そして内部はそれを吸収するのに十分な長さになります
and its body is back where it should be
そしてその体はあるべき場所に戻った
like muscles
筋肉のような
Or do the necessary synthesis of each part
または各パーツの必要な合成を行います
so not a problem
だから問題ない
that lady
あの女性
to the back
後ろへ
Okay, then there is another classmate behind you
はい、あなたの後ろに別のクラスメートがいます
Miss
逃す
Hello Dr. Ann
こんにちは、アン博士
I have seen it said here
ここでそう言われているのを見たことがあります
Has published more than 300 academic papers
300以上の学術論文を発表している
Among them, you are focusing on the diet and genetic inheritance of metabolic diseases in the elderly
その中で、あなたは高齢者の食事と代謝性疾患の遺伝に焦点を当てています。
here factor
ここの要素
Where can we see your paper
あなたの論文はどこで見られますか
All of our papers are written in English
私たちの論文はすべて英語で書かれています
Internationally
国際的に
so
それで
what kind of journal
どのような日記ですか
various periodicals
各種定期刊行物
So I don't know about your little show We have a place in academia called
だから私はあなたの小さなショーについて知りません 学術界には、と呼ばれる場所があります
P-POP-MAD P-U-B-M-E-D
P-POP-MAD P-U-B-M-E-D
this
これ
You type P-U-B-M-E-D in Google
Google で P-U-B-M-E-D と入力します
you will go in
あなたは入ります
Then you call Pan Wenhan
それからパン・ウェンハンに電話します
My English name
私の英語名
my english name may be
私の英語名はもしかしたら
W-E-N
ウェン
you just call my name
あなたはただ私の名前を呼んでください
You can if you can type my name in Chinese on Google
Google に私の名前を中国語で入力していただければ入力できます
you can see my english name
私の英語名が見えます
you type my name in
あなたは私の名前を入力します
All my papers will come out
私の書類はすべて出てくるでしょう
that he
彼が
But I'm afraid you don't understand
でもあなたには理解できないと思います
it's all in english
すべて英語です
right
右
I want to focus on what is the special topic of this article
この記事の特別なトピックは何かに焦点を当てたいと思います
his
他的
For example, there is a
たとえば、次のようなものがあります。
You said it was today, right?
今日って言ったよね？
no
いいえ
that is
あれは
In more than 300 articles, he
彼は 300 以上の記事の中で、
Emphasis on this article
この記事の強調
OK
OK
This doesn't seem to be the focus
ここが焦点ではないようです
He said it was this series, this series
彼はこれがこのシリーズだ、このシリーズだと言いました
this series
このシリーズ
right
右
this kind
この種
theme
テーマ
right
右
There are various papers
色々な紙があります
Thanks
ありがとう
I think
私が思うに
Take his question and ask it by the way
彼の質問を聞いて、ところで聞いてみてください
Now the question you just focused on is
さて、あなたが今注目した質問は、
Nutrition for Cardiovascular Metabolism
心血管代謝のための栄養
then ask
その後尋ねます
Where is the hottest direction right now
今最も熱い方向はどこですか
Cardiovascular
心臓血管
his
他的
for example
例えば
people with coronary artery disease
冠動脈疾患のある人
in terms of diet
ダイエットの面で
what is the latest theory
最新の理論は何ですか
because it is not said recently
最近言われてないから
Sometimes Cholesterol Is Not All That Causes
コレステロールだけが原因ではないこともある
Causes of hardening of the arteries of the heart
心臓の動脈硬化の原因
The latest theory
最新の理論
In fact, there are many
実際にはたくさんあります
Let me put it this way, I know you may be quite interested in cholesterol.
こう言っておきますが、皆さんはコレステロールに非常に興味があるかもしれません。
high blood cholesterol
血中コレステロールが高い
it cures heart disease
それは心臓病を治す
And that's basically narrowing this canister artery.
そしてそれは基本的にこのキャニスター動脈を狭めることになります。
That theory has not been disproved until now.
その理論は現在まで反証されていません。
still exist
まだ存在します
Now the latest controversy is that
さて、最近の論争は、
can you eat eggs
卵は食べられますか
high blood cholesterol
血中コレステロールが高い
It will definitely cure cardiovascular disease
心臓病は必ず治る
Increased risk of cardiovascular disease
心血管疾患のリスクの増加
it's ok
大丈夫です
The problem is that eating eggs
問題は卵を食べることです
Will it increase blood cholesterol
血中コレステロールが増加しますか
yes the problem is here
はい、問題はここにあります
What about this
これはどうですか
A correct statement is that it should be
正しい記述は、こうあるべきであるということです。
That is to say, the cholesterol content of the egg itself
つまり、卵自体のコレステロール量は
Affects the blood to a moderate extent
血液に中程度の影響を与える
the degree is not high
程度は高くない
The most important factor affecting blood cholesterol
血中コレステロールに影響を与える最も重要な要素
is saturated fatty acid
飽和脂肪酸です
that is, the butter
つまりバターです
For example, eating butter
たとえば、バターを食べると、
And red meat, pork fat
赤身肉、豚脂
There is CTS oil, coconut oil
CTSオイル、ココナッツオイルあり
These oils and the backlash just mentioned
これらのオイルと先ほど述べたバックラッシュ
These are the ones that cause the blood to be high
これらは血液の増加を引き起こすものです
So why did you talk about eggs before and don't talk about eggs now?
では、なぜ以前は卵について話していたのに、今は卵について話さないのですか?
It's just that the diet of human beings in the past is a little different from what it is now
ただ、昔の人間の食生活は今とは少し違うようです。
in the previous time and space
前の時間と空間で
This egg has a greater impact
この卵の方がインパクトが大きい
Now the time-space egg has less influence
現在、時空卵の影響力は小さくなりました
So the same research is repeated and redone
同じ研究が繰り返され、やり直しになる
Now slowly find that the impact of eggs is getting smaller
今では、卵の影響が徐々に小さくなっていることがわかります
so it will follow
それで続きます
plus Americans
加えてアメリカ人
Because this suggestion is from the United States
この提案はアメリカからのものなので、
Cholesterol drops across the U.S.
アメリカ全土でコレステロールが低下
Since the United States of America has changed the recommendation to say
アメリカ合衆国が次のように勧告を変更したため、
Eating eggs is not that serious
卵を食べることはそれほど深刻ではありません
The most important thing is to protect the fat
一番大切なのは脂肪を守ること
still say so
まだそう言う
But this is for ordinary people
でもこれは一般人向けです
If you are a person with already high cholesterol in Cholesterolology
コレステロール学ですでにコレステロールが高い人の場合
However, it is still necessary to minimize
ただし、最小限に抑える必要がある
or should you say
それとも言うべきですか
if you find you eat eggs
卵を食べていることに気づいたら
you can test yourself
自分自身を試すことができます
just go up
ただ上がってください
should be reduced
減らすべきだ
do you understand
わかりますか
it points to common people's advice
それは一般人のアドバイスを指します
It is still different from the patient's suggestion
患者の提案とはまだ異なる
so i don't know what else
だから他に何があるかわからない
other salary
その他の給料
Because everyone does a lot of different research
みんな色々調べてるから
For example, what I am currently doing
例えば、今私がやっていること
There are two relatively new
比較的新しいのが２つあります
I'm talking about a mineral
鉱物の話をしているのですが
minerals are beautiful
鉱物は美しい
The protective effect of this beauty on heart diseases
この美しさの心臓病に対する保護効果
I'm currently discussing
現在話し合い中です
Actually I have published a
実は私も出版したことがあります
Journal of the American Academy of Clinical Nutrition
米国臨床栄養学会誌
I help this patient
私はこの患者を助けます
patients who have already had a stroke
すでに脳卒中を起こしている患者
I scan his beauty every day
私は毎日彼の美しさをチェックしています
A month later his stroke recovery was better than no one
1か月後、彼の脳卒中からの回復は誰よりも良好でした
is twice as good
2倍良いです
It has been published here
こちらで公開されました
Well, I actually found that this beauty may affect blood flow
実はこの美しさは血流に影響を与える可能性があることが分かりました
So I'm doing a study recently which is
それで最近研究をしているのですが、
head and beauty
頭と美しさ
See if it affects the blood flow rate
血流量に影響を与えるかどうかを確認する
that affects this
それがこれに影響する
If it affects the blood flow velocity from the neck to the brain
首から脳への血流速度に影響を与える場合
We now have to go further
これからはさらに前進する必要があります
Will it affect dementia
認知症に影響はありますか
For example, this is my current
たとえば、これは私の現在のものです
a new study being done
新しい研究が行われています
But I dare not tell you now
でも今はあえて言わない
I'm not done yet
まだ終えていません
Another research we are doing is
私たちが行っているもう一つの研究は、
After making oil to fry it
揚げ油を作ってから
fried food
揚げ物
Will it affect a variety of different diseases
さまざまな病気に影響を与えるのでしょうか
Then we found that
それから私たちはそれを発見しました
May be some fried it's ok
揚げ物でも大丈夫ですよ
some fried
揚げたもの
So if this result comes out in the future
なので今後この結果が出たら
i will
私はこれから
just maybe for example
例えばそれは可能です
How do you tell the public when you hold a press conference?
記者会見をするとき、国民にどのように伝えますか？
OK if you want fried food
揚げ物が食べたいならOK
you must use this oil for frying
揚げ物にはこの油を使わなければなりません
But fried food no matter what
でも揚げ物はどう見ても
just good fried
ちょうど良い揚げ物
There will also be some problems, so I will explain them clearly to you.
いくつか問題点も出てきますので、わかりやすく解説していきます。
Which oil can be fried and which oil can not be fried
揚げられる油と揚げられない油はどれですか
Then its best to fry as much as you can eat in a week
それなら1週間で食べられる量だけ揚げるのがベストです
That's another research I'm doing
それは私が行っている別の研究です
That of course means that if it is fried for too long
もちろん、揚げ時間が長すぎると、
This means that qualitative variability is another possible problem
これは、質的な変動が別の潜在的な問題であることを意味します
right
右
We just had a problem here
ここで問題が発生しました
there is a question
質問があります
there is a classmate
同級生がいます
right
右
I want to ask Teacher Pan about that
それについてパン先生に聞きたいです
Why do some elderly people's feet are particularly prone to cramp
一部の高齢者の足が特にけいれんしやすいのはなぜですか
Does it have anything to do with diet?
ダイエットと何か関係があるのでしょうか？
The problem of cramping is also
けいれんの問題も
In fact, sometimes a symptom
実際に症状が現れることもあります
Actually very
実はとても
It should be said that non-specific is
非特異的であると言うべきです
Usually we are talking about causal inference
通常、私たちは因果推論について話します
means that A will cause B
AがBを引き起こすことを意味します
But is B just because of A
しかし、B は A のせいでしょうか？
it's hard to say
言うのが難しい
Your question now is a little bit
今の質問はちょっとしたものです
For example, it's not the same as virology.
たとえば、ウイルス学とは異なります。
Hepatitis B Virus
B型肝炎ウイルス
can cause hepatitis B
B型肝炎を引き起こす可能性がある
if you have hepatitis B
B型肝炎に罹患している場合
You are the hepatitis B virus
あなたはB型肝炎ウイルスです
But now the cramp problem is A, B, C, D, E
しかし今のけいれんの問題は A、B、C、D、E です
There's a whole bunch of them that can give you a cramp
けいれんがたくさんあります
so i'm having a hard time answering
だから答えるのに困っている
But if we talk about the diet
しかし、ダイエットの話になると、
often
頻繁
caused by electrolyte imbalance
電解質のアンバランスが原因
calcium for example
例えばカルシウム
For example, beauty
たとえば、美しさ
For example, A
たとえば、A
but i can't decide
でも決められない
it should probably mean
それはおそらく意味するはずです
Nutritionally related is electrolyte imbalance
栄養に関係するのは電解質のアンバランスです
Imbalance can cause cramps in the elderly
バランスの崩れは高齢者にけいれんを引き起こす可能性があります
And you see athletes running
そしてアスリートが走っているのが見えます
Does the long hair cramp at the end?
長い髪は最後に窮屈になりますか？
That's also an electrolyte imbalance.
それも電解質のバランスの崩れです。
Okay, we'll have this question later
わかりました、この質問は後で行います
Teacher Pan, I want to ask for advice
パン先生、アドバイスが聞きたいのですが
That's what I saw mentioned in different places
色々なところで言及されているのを見たことがありますが、
can't drink too much milk
牛乳はあまり飲めない
Because of the hormone he contains
彼に含まれるホルモンのせいで
can cause cancer
がんを引き起こす可能性がある
And this is because the milk in the process of releasing oxygen
これは、牛乳が酸素を放出する過程にあるためです
given antibiotics
抗生物質を投与された
Another saying is that
もう一つの言い伝えは、
The order in which we eat protein foods is linked to weight control
プロテイン食品を食べる順序は体重管理に関係しています
Protein should be eaten first or after
プロテインは最初または後に摂取する必要があります
Can affect weight control
体重管理に影響を与える可能性がある
Please help me with this question
この質問はあなたに尋ねます
OK
OK
The first one is about the problem of not being able to eat this kind of milk
一つ目は、このような牛乳が食べられない問題についてです。
This is indeed very popular on the Internet
実はこれ、ネット上で大人気なんです
We often even I often receive emails to see such problems
私もそのような問題を確認するメールを頻繁に受け取ります
From the standpoint of our nutritionists
私たち栄養士の立場から
We think it's a stigma against milk
私たちはそれが牛乳に対する偏見だと考えています
it's a pity
それは残念だ
a very good food
とても良い食べ物
The result is stigmatized like this
結果はこうやって非難される
I don't understand where these things come from
こういったものがどこから来たのか理解できません
But I can also imagine
でも想像することもできる
Why do ordinary people easily accept such a concept
なぜ一般の人はそのような概念を簡単に受け入れるのでしょうか
just because milk has a problem
牛乳に問題があるからといって
so-called lactose intolerance
いわゆる乳糖不耐症
If you are lactose intolerant
乳糖不耐症の場合
words in the short term
短期的な言葉
You do have some lactose in the upgrade
アップグレードには乳糖が含まれています
Lactose cannot be metabolized in the body
乳糖は体内で代謝されません
may cause some
何らかの原因となる可能性があります
a symptom of diarrhea
下痢の症状
even some bad microbes
悪い微生物さえも
growth of intestinal flora
腸内フローラの成長
make you uncomfortable
あなたを不快にする
like flatulence or something
鼓腸か何かのように
will definitely have this problem
間違いなくこの問題が発生します
so when you eat it you don't feel well
だから食べると気分が悪くなる
Then when paired with these rumors on the Internet
そして、インターネット上のこれらの噂と組み合わせると、
you'll feel it's right
あなたはそれが正しいと感じるでしょう
So cause this phenomenon
だからこの現象を引き起こす
But if we look at big data
しかしビッグデータを見てみると
For example, if you look at big data
例えばビッグデータを見てみると
We still have a lot of data like nutritional surveys
栄養調査などのデータはまだたくさんあります
Let's analyze domestic people who drink milk
国内の牛乳を飲む人を分析してみよう
His health is better
彼の健康状態は良くなりました
And he's a protein
そして彼はプロテインです
if there is a milk drinker
牛乳を飲む人がいたら
he is usually less fat
彼は通常、それほど太っていない
He is less prone to some metabolic syndrome
彼はメタボリックシンドロームの傾向が少ない
So he actually if you analyze the data
データを分析すると、彼は実際に
he's all right
彼は大丈夫です
But ordinary people experience
しかし、普通の人が経験するのは、
Seeing this makes me feel uncomfortable
こういうの見ると不快な気持ちになる
So his problem is because of lactose intolerance
つまり、彼の問題は乳糖不耐症によるものです
Then lactose intolerance can be overcome
そうすれば乳糖不耐症も克服できる
His method of overcoming is
彼の克服方法は、
you start with a small amount
少量から始めます
like me personally for a while
しばらくの間私のように
just not busy
ただ忙しくないだけ
We are too busy to pay attention to this matter
私たちは仕事でとても忙しいので、この件に注意を払いませんでした
So then I can't drink milk
じゃあ牛乳も飲めないのか
So then I because I'm a nutritionist myself
それで、私は自分自身が栄養士なので、
I said I made it look like this
こんな感じに作ったって言ってた
So I started cultivating my own lactose-digesting enzymes
そこで私は自分で乳糖分解酵素を培養し始めました
how to do that
どうやってするか
That is to say, today you make a cup of tea, for example
つまり、たとえば今日、あなたはお茶を一杯入れます。
I will let it go today
今日は手放します
I like to use milk powder
粉ミルクを使うのが好きです
because it is more convenient
そのほうが便利だから
Just put a soup and a pool of powdered tea milk powder
スープと抹茶ミルクのプールを入れるだけ
You'll be fine if you drink it
飲めば大丈夫だよ
Then two o'clock the next day
それから翌日の2時
drink like this for a week
このまま一週間飲み続ける
i can take two hours
2時間かかっても大丈夫です
next week at three o'clock
来週の3時に
then four o'clock
それから4時
no problem
問題ない
Just one time to cultivate it like this
このように栽培するのは一度だけです
you can drink later
後で飲んでもいいよ
This is such a point of view
こういう視点もあるよな
So our nutritionists' dietary guidelines in Taiwan
台湾の栄養士による食事ガイドライン
We recommend a day alone
一人の日をオススメします
one to two cups
1〜2カップ
that's one and a half cups
それは1.5カップです
but i have to tell you
でも、言わなければなりません
That's what I'm working on recently
それが最近私が取り組んでいることです
that is climate change
それは気候変動です
Then let's read the latest article I recently read
それでは最近読んだ最新記事を読んでみましょう
started to talk about an issue
ある問題について話し始めた
This is an idea of sacrificing the small self for the sake of the big self
これは大きな自分のために小さな自分を犠牲にするという考え方です
That is to say, if there is not enough food in the world in the future,
つまり、将来、世界に十分な食料がなくなったら、
What kind of food shall we eat
さて、どんな料理を食べましょうか？
it maintains health
それは健康を維持します
And then to ensure global food security
そして世界の食糧安全保障を確保するために
everyone has food
誰もが食べ物を持っています
that such a food
そんな食べ物とは
Just be less animalistic
もう少し動物的になってください
less animal
動物が少ない
But it's not about eating bad food
でも、それは悪いものを食べることではありません
Then when I was reading these papers
それから私がこれらの論文を読んでいたとき
Discover their recommendations intermediate for milk
牛乳の中間の推奨事項を確認してください
Do you want to see how good cheese Westerners eat?
西洋人がどれほどおいしいチーズを食べるか見てみたいですか?
Pizza Burger Milk Coffee
ピザバーガーミルクコーヒー
Good milk is there
いい牛乳あるよ
but they say
しかし彼らは言う
in the future they will wish to say
将来彼らはこう言いたいだろう
That's the amount of a glass of milk a day
それは1日コップ1杯の牛乳に相当します
just fine
大丈夫です
This is for environmental protection
これは環境保護のためです
When considering this climate change
この気候変動を考えるとき
Let me tell you about this latest trend
この最新トレンドについてお話します
Is that glass of milk good for health?
そのコップ一杯の牛乳は健康に良いですか?
It must be possible
きっと可能だ
because you are in that situation
あなたがその状況にいるから
you will go with other food
他の食べ物と一緒に行きます
Can soy milk replace milk
豆乳は牛乳の代わりになりますか
soy milk
豆乳
In our current dietary guidelines
現在の食事ガイドラインでは
If you follow the current dietary guidelines when eating
食事の際に現在の食事ガイドラインに従っている場合
it won't work
それはうまくいきません
Because we plan it as your calcium
あなたのカルシウムとして企画しますので
And your B complex and some minerals
そしてあなたのB複合体といくつかのミネラル
Like armor and beauty are derived from milk
鎧も美しさも乳から生まれるように
Then soybeans
それから大豆
Definitely delivers the same amount of protein
確実に同じ量のタンパク質を供給します
But the calcium in soybeans
しかし、大豆に含まれるカルシウムは、
Much less than these B groups
これらのBグループよりもはるかに少ない
So in the future if we want to do this
したがって、将来的にこれをやりたい場合は、
So we often learn as we do
したがって、私たちはしばしばそうしながら学びます
One more topic to talk about is
もう一つ話すべきトピックは、
with added soymilk
豆乳を加えたもの
It's this soy milk that adds some
それを加えるのがこの豆乳です
Even food rich in group B is fine.
グループBが豊富な食べ物でも大丈夫です。
Or add vitamin calcium and D
またはビタミンカルシウムとDを追加します
This can be considered in the future
将来的にはこれも考えられる
It's just that we have had some conversations with manufacturers
メーカーといくつか話し合っているだけです
The food world they have so far had no will
これまでの食の世界には意志がなかった
launch this thing
これを起動します
So in the future we will see what kind of method to use
したがって、今後どのような方法を使用するか見てみましょう
Encourage the so-called matching with milk
いわゆるミルクとのマッチングを促す
It is soy milk with exactly the same nutritional value
栄養価は全く同じ豆乳です
Our countrymen also like to drink
私たちの同胞もお酒が好きです
So I think this is a direction we will work hard in the future.
ですので、今後はその方向で頑張っていきたいと思います。
ok i think it's about time
よし、そろそろ時間だと思う
So let me give you a preview of the next self-thought feast
それでは、次回の自主企画のプレビューをさせてください
It was the lecture given by President Zhu Jiahua Ke Puye on May 28
5月28日に朱家華柯濤学部長が行った講演です。
Wang Baoguan Banquet Room, the Center of Environmental Change
環境変化の中心地、王宝関宴会場
He used to be the director of the center
彼はかつてセンターの所長をしていた
The secret of the coming and going storm in the long wind
長風の中で、去ったり来たりする嵐の秘密
Everyone is welcome to sign up
どなたでもご登録いただけます
Thanks again Professor Pan Honghuan
パン・ホンファン教授に改めて感謝します
Thank you.
ありがとう。